-=THE LAST FANTASY=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=TLF字幕组=- 翻译：crazymelody  micezhang 校对：micezhang
(CHATTERING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(GRUNTING)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(PANTING)
(EXCLAIMING)
“片名：政局密云”
哦，帕迪・墨菲死的那晚
(CAL SINGING) Oh, the night that Paddy Murphy died
是我会铭记的一晚
Is a night I'll never forget
有些人喝的烂醉
Some of the boys got loaded drunk
而且还没有清醒
And they ain't got sober yet
只要有酒
As long as a bottle was passed around
每个人都会很愉快
Every man was feeling gay
带着风笛的奥里瑞
O'Leary came with the bagpipes
演奏了一些乐曲
Some music for to play
他们用这种方式表达对帕迪・墨菲的敬意
That's how they showed their respect for Paddy Murphy
他们用这种方式表达荣誉感和自豪
That's how they showed their honor and their pride
他们说这是罪与耻辱
They said it was a sin and shame
他们互使眼色
And they winked at one another
帕特・墨菲死的那晚
And every drink in the place was full
每个酒杯都被斟满
The night Pat Murphy died
当墨非太太坐在角落里
As Mrs. Murphy sat in the corner
倾诉悲伤时
Pouring out her grief
凯利和同伙在街上扫荡
Kelly and his gang came tearing down the street
他们冲进一间空房子
They went into an empty room
偷了一瓶威士忌
And a bottle of whiskey stole
他们把酒瓶放在尸体旁
They put the bottle with the corpse
让威士忌保鲜
To keep that whiskey cold
他们用这种方式表达敬意
That's how they showed their respect for...
那白人被送到医院去了
They took the white kid to the hospital.
他现在昏迷
He's in a coma.
长官，你应该和他家人联系一下
Officer, you should check in with the family.
不管你卖什么，我都不会买的
Whatever you're selling, I ain't buying.
好了，各位，你们可以走了
Okay, guys, take off.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
咖啡是为记者的朋友免费提供的
Coffee's free for friends of the press.
听说地铁警局弹道分析组的人刚走
I heard Metro ballistics was just here.
谁告诉你的？
Who told you that?
你刚刚的反应
You just did.
能透露嫌犯的名字吗？
You got the names of the victims for me?
你简直是开玩笑
You gotta be kidding me.
我肯定会知道的
You know I'm gonna find out anyway.
但不是从我这里
Not from me.
好吧，我提问，你回答是或否，如何？
Okay. You want to play a little confirm or deny?
卡尔，我没功夫跟你玩游戏
I'm not playing this game with you, Cal.
听着，唐，我要混口饭吃，明白吗？
Look, Don, I got a living to make, all right?
我要养家糊口，还要喂金鱼
I got mouths to feed, goldfish.
替你保密，好吗？
(CHUCKLING)
No names, no quotes, all right?
好吧
Okay.
两名受害人，一个杀手？
Two victims, one shooter?
是
Confirm.
一死一伤？
One dead, one in the hospital?
是
Confirm.
与毒品有关？
Drug related?
是，但是有待进一步查证
Confirm, but deny later if I have to.
早上好 早上好，先生
Good morning. WOMAN: Good morning, sir.
好吧，我知道我迟到了
Okay, I'm late. I know.
你们不用提醒我
I don't need to be reminded of it.
任务发布的备忘我已经看过很多次了
I've been over the briefing notes 1,000 times.
- 史蒂芬 - 怎么了？
Stephen. Yes?
刚刚地铁警察局来电
Metro Police just called.
什么情况？
What?
索尼娅・贝克今天早上乘地铁时出意外死了
Sonia Baker was killed in an accident on the Metro this morning.
他们通过员工徽章辨认了身份
They identified her by her staff badge.
这对我们所有人来说都是噩耗
Horrible news for all of us.
但是，史蒂芬，我们马上就要开始了
But, Stephen, we're scheduled to start now.
你想怎么做？
What do you want to do?
“尖兵集团”
“华盛顿环球报” “新媒体集团旗下”
早上好，匹兹堡
WOMAN: Morning, Pittsburgh.
尹瑟
Yinzer.
卡尔，早上好
Cal. Morning.
跟我说说这次枪击案的情况
Talk to me about this shooting.
有一个人幸存
You know, one guy's still alive.
德尚・斯塔格？
Deshaun Stagg?
不是，他死了
No, he's dead.
是弗农・桑杜，骑自行车的那个
The other guy on the bike, Vernon Sando.
嘿，吉恩，我写的那篇初稿你看了吗？
Hey, Gene, did you read the guinea pig piece I filed?
好的，我会看的，菲里斯
Yeah, I'll get to it, Ferris.
- 那篇文章很不错，讲的是人类利益 - 好的，人类利益
Because it's a great human interest story. Yeah, human interest.
那么到底是怎么一回事？
So what's the deal?
斯塔格的毒品交易除出了岔子 而这骑车的家伙碰巧经过？
Stagg's drug deal goes wrong, and this guy just rides by?
没错，我想大概就是那样吧
Yeah, something like that, I think.
那是一个了不起的讲述生存的故事
That's a remarkable feat of survival.
呃，至少知道事发地点
Well, at least it's got a little bit of a zip code to it.
乔治城是重点，对吗？
Georgetown's the angle, right?
不对，不对，重点是弗农・桑杜…
No, no, the angle is that this guy Vernon Sando
是杜克大学的工商管理硕士
has got an MBA from Duke.
他骑自行车做什么？
What's he doing on a bike?
他打算买一家批萨连锁店
He's buying a pizza franchise.
在头六个月，他们要求你骑自行车
You know, they make you ride the bike
学最基本的东西
for the first six months, learn the ropes.
他结了婚，生了两个孩子，还按揭贷款 是最普通的公民
He's got a wife, two kids, mortgage, total citizen.
他情况如何？
What's his condition?
很危急，没有反应 第三段，他处于昏迷状态
Critical, non-reactive. Paragraph three. He's in a coma.
好的，有情况通知我
Okay, let me know.
我会的
I will.
早上好
(CLEARING THRO AT) Good morning.
ALL: Good morning.
欢迎各位出席这次对私营安保承包商 “尖兵集团”的听证会
Welcome to our hearings with private security contractor PointCorp,
此次会议是调查国防部的…
part of the inquiry into the Defense Department's
民营化与外包任务的一部分
privatization and outsourcing practices.
在我们开始之前，我刚接到了一个噩耗
Before we begin, I've just received some terrible news.
索尼娅・贝克
Sonia Baker,
委员会的首席研究员
who was the lead researcher for this committee
同时也是我的重要工作伙伴 于今早身亡
and a valued member of my staff, died this morning.
(CROWD MURMURING)
她的死因尚无定论
The circumstances of her death are not yet clear.
我要向她的家人表示慰唁
Well, I'd like to send my condolences to her family.
(SIGHS)
我的天，他哭了？
(EXHALING)
Oh, my God, are those tears?
我赌50美元，他和她有一腿
50 bucks says he's balling her.
50美元？ 等下，你本来就欠我50美元
50 bucks? Wait, you owe me 50 bucks.
糟糕的国会议员，太糟糕了
Bad Congressman! Bad.
真是个烂人！
What a scumball!
有没有谁能给我张她的照片
GENE: Somebody get me a picture of the girl.
希望她不是157厘米 136公斤
Let's hope she's not 5'2" and 300 pounds.
吉恩，吉恩，你为什么老是痴迷胖女人呢？
Gene, Gene, what is your obsession with fat girls?
如果你想和皮特做的话，只说就是了
If you want to have sex with Pete, you should just say it.
今晚不行，我头痛
Not tonight, I got a headache.
说吧，说吧，吉恩，说啊
HANK: Say it. Say it, Gene. Say it.
照片！照片！
GENE: Picture! Picture!
起初大家对这场悲剧的反应…
REPORTER... Reaction to the tragic death was initially,
是震惊，这是人之常情
and understandably, one of shock,
但是贝克小姐的死亡一经宣布
yet questions immediately began to surface
问题随即出现
as soon as Ms. Baker's death was announced.
“网络部”
嘿，乔，我是环球报的卡尔・麦卡弗雷
Hey, Joe, Cal McAffrey over at the Globe.
是关于昨晚乔治城发生的枪击事件
Just calling about that shooting in Georgetown last night.
我听说死者有前科，抢过几次钱包
I heard the dead kid had a couple of priors as a purse snatcher.
有没有具体消息？
Got any more details for me?
回打给我？ 行，行，你也是
Call me back? Yeah, yeah. You, too.
嘿，问你个问题
Hey, I got a question for you.
史蒂芬・柯林斯
Stephen Collins.
他是你的老朋友，没错吧？
He's an old friend of yours, is that right?
没错
Yeah.
我叫黛拉，黛拉・弗雷娅
I'm Della. Della Frye.
国会博客是我执笔的
I write the Capitol Hill blog.
好 网络部的
All right. Online side.
我很欣赏你写的文章
I'm a big fan of your work.
我正在写一篇文章，是关于政界的…
So, I'm writing this piece on personal relationships
私人关系
in the political sphere,
“权力中央的单身女人” 类似那样的内容
"single girl in the corridors of power" kind of thing,
也许你已经知道
and as you probably know,
今早在你朋友的听证会上…
there was this incident this morning on the Hill,
所发生的小插曲
at your friend's hearing.
你是不是有问题要问我？
Is there a question on the horizon?
没错，你今天联系过他吗？
Yeah. Have you spoken to him today?
你想把我也扯进你的文章中吗？
Are you trying to make me part of your story?
不是，我试图寻找背景材料
No. I'm trying to get a little context.
背景材料，回复：丑闻？
Context, re: Dirt?
你觉得他和那女人有染吗？
Well, do you think he was having an affair with that girl?
天啊，黛拉
Gee, Della.
嗯
Yeah.
我不知道，在下定论前
I don't know. I'd have to read a couple of blogs
我得看几个博客
before I could form an opinion.
行，谢谢你的帮助
Okay. Thanks for your help.
不客气！
Anytime!
国会可能再掀风波
ANCHORWOMAN 1... Capitol Hill may be rocked with another bombshell.
（美味丑闻独家报道： 史蒂芬・柯林斯：震惊的事实）
Speculation is rife that Stephen Collins
盛传史蒂芬・柯林斯… （照片文字：被捕）
有可能与今早丧命的年轻助手…
may have been romantically linked
（性、谎言和政治）
with the young aide found dead this morning.
有暧昧关系
His spokesmen call this another political cloud...
他的发言人声称这又是一层政治阴影…
对柯林斯来说，这是最坏的时机
ANCHORMAN... The timing couldn't be worse for Collins.
他需要最大的政治影响力
He needs all the political leverage he can get
帮助他调查国防部的…
as he begins looking into the Defense Department's
军事外包行为
outsourcing practices.
“尖兵集团”是一个颇具争议的 私营军事承包商
ANCHORWOMAN 2... Called mercenaries by some and saviors by others,
一些人认为它惟利是图 而其他则认为它是救世主
PointCorp, the controversial private military contractor,
据说该公司是国防部的在伊拉克和阿富汗的…
is said to be the biggest beneficiary
军事外包活动中的最大受益者
in the Defense Department's outsourcing in Iraq and Afghanistan.
柯林斯与他大学时代女友结婚已有10年
Collins, who'd been married for 10 years to his college sweetheart,
据猜测他回绝了贝克小姐的要求 留在妻子身边
is thought to have refused to leave his wife for Miss Baker.
说正经的
GEORGE: Brass tacks.
你是否和这个女人有染？
Were you having a relationship with this girl?
是的
Yes,
对于这一切，我十分抱歉
and I can't tell you how sorry I am about all of this.
好
Okay.
我请了安德鲁来帮我们…
I've asked Andrew here to help us
从媒体的角度处理事情
handle things from a media point of view.
如果有人能帮我们避过风头的话，那就是他了
If anyone can steer us through this, he can.
接下来的72小时将会很残酷
Well, the next 72 hours are gonna be brutal.
你要有心理准备
You ought to brace yourself for that.
你将会暂时成为众矢之的 一切对政治的不满都会发泄到你身上
For a while, you're gonna be everything that's wrong with politics.
史蒂夫，你依旧很优秀
You're still a star, Steve.
党会帮助它的明星人物的
The party takes care of its stars.
你只需暂时保持低姿态
You just have to lay low for a while.
多低？
How low?
很低
Low.
任何引起对你高度关注的事都要避免
Nothing that would bring any undue attention to yourself.
譬如说，听证会
At the hearings, for instance.
我们还没有处理完“尖兵集团”的事宜
We're not finished with PointCorp.
的确没有，但是你的任务结束了
No, but you are.
如果你现在向那些人开火进攻的话
If you open up fire on those guys right now,
那看上去不会像是你管理有方
that's not gonna look like good governance,
反而只像是在蓄意分散公众注意力
just a calculated distraction.
你的妻子肯跟你讲话了吗？
Is your wife speaking to you?
不，现在还不肯
No, not right now.
那么你就有首要任务了，不是吗？
Then that's job one, isn't it?
尹瑟！她知道你收到消息了
Yinzer! She knows you got the message,
而且她知道你在
and she knows you're in the building.
是的
Yes.
“永远不要相信编辑”
早上好
Morning.
进展如何？ 他到底和她有没有私情？
So, where are we? Was he knobbing her or not?
早上好，卡姆
Morning, Cam.
你真的很滑稽，每次你的朋友竞选连任…
It's funny about you. Every time your friend runs for reelection
或者是主持听证会
or conducts a hearing,
你都是不断提及他的名字 直到我们肯报道他的消息
you drop his name to me until we give him some coverage.
但是等到他终于做了件…
But he finally does something
有望能提高报纸销量的事情
that actually might sell some newspapers,
你却不说话了
you're rendered mute.
前后太不一致了
It's incongruous.
不，不是这样的
No, it is not.
是前后矛盾
It's inconsistent.
别给我耍滑头
(SCOFFS) Don't be an ass.
你觉得如何？
What do you think?
那些是我们准备用来转型的创意
Those are the ideas for our facelift.
我知道，我知道，全是瞎话
I know. I know. It's crap.
我们的新老板很奇怪
Our new owners have this odd idea
他觉得我们应该是盈利的
that we ought to be turning a profit.
是的，呃，我听说我们的网络部成绩不错
Yeah, well, I hear our online side is doing great.
我不是那种会注意…
I mean, not like I'm the kind of guy
那类事情的人
who would notice that sort of thing,
但是，我在这待了，多少，15年？
but I've been here, what, 15 years?
我用的16年前的电脑
I use a 16-year-old computer.
她来这里15分钟
She's been here 15 minutes,
而她拥有的装备可以用来发射俄罗斯卫星
and she could launch a Russian satellite with the gear she's got.
没错，她告诉我你很让人讨厌，就像猪一样
Yeah, she told me you behaved like a pig.
这话有点过
That's too strong.
呃，讨厌兮兮的
Well, piggish.
我只是给她看了我的猪鼻子
I showed her a little snout.
碰巧我很喜欢黛拉・弗雷娅小姐
Well, I happen to like Ms. Della Frye.
而且，没错，的确是我派她去…
And, yes, I did send her down there
你那打探点消息的
to winkle something out of you.
她欲求强烈，对工资要求不高 但是她却能每个小时都发稿
She's hungry, she's cheap, and she churns out copy every hour.
是的，我知道，我只会坐等 薪水高，而且效率低下
Yeah, I know. I'm overfed, I'm too expensive, and I take way too long.
是的，确实如此
Yes, you do.
我曾是史蒂芬・柯林斯的大学舍友
I was Stephen Collins' roommate in college.
但我现在不和他住在一起
I don't live with him now.
那很可惜，不是吗？
Well, that's a shame, isn't it?
是啊，那我和他的绯闻就能提升报纸销量了
Yeah, 'cause that could sell some newspapers.
贝克小姐今早于华盛顿地铁…
ANCHORMAN 1... Miss Baker died this morning in an apparent accident
一起意外中身亡
on the D.C. Metro.
自杀的可能性尚未被排除
Suicide has not been ruled out.
种种迹象显示这是一起自杀事件
(CHATTERING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
It appears to be a suicide.
此案有关人员透露国会议员柯林斯…
People close to the case say that Congressman Collins,
“利用了”这个年轻的女孩 从而导致了她今日的自杀
quote, "took advantage" of this young girl, resulting in today's suicide.
- 自杀 - 自杀
ANCHORMAN 2... Suicide. ANCHORMAN 3... Suicide.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
我知道你在想…
So, I know you're thinking,
“这人一定是绝望透顶了，才在这里出现”
"This guy's gotta be pretty desperate to show up here."
不对，我是在想我终于有机会把…
No, I was thinking I can finally give you back
你落在我车里的“洛克希音乐乐队”的CD 还给你了
that Roxy Music CD you left in my car.
那张CD落你车里了？ 我还在找呢
Is that where that one went? I was looking for that.
有三十几个记者扎营在我家门口
I got three dozen reporters camped in front of my place.
如果可以，我会去别的地方
I'd go somewhere else,
但是我无处可去
but I don't have anywhere else to go.
- 进来吧 - 谢谢
Come in. Thanks.
你重新装修过了
I see you redecorated.
是啊，我把那张沙发移了几英尺
Yeah. I moved that couch a couple of feet.
看着不错
Looks good.
你不打算问我怎么会这么愚蠢吗？
Aren't you gonna ask me how I could be so stupid?
- 马上就问 - 好的
In a minute. Okay.
在过去的三年里，我与别人合作提交两份议案
You know, I co-sponsored two bills in the last three years.
我正和同事起草另一份议案
I'm in the middle of co-authoring another one,
而这份议案也将让我名垂青史
and this is what I'm gonna be remembered for.
我这次得到的曝光率将比…
I'm gonna get more coverage on this
我余生所做的任何事情都要多
than anything else I do for the rest of my life.
公职就是这样的
The nature of the beast, public office.
好吧
Okay.
听着卡尔
Look, Cal,
我知道上次见面我说了些不该说的
I know the last time I saw you, I said a few things.
嘿
Hey.
是我活该，都怪我自己
I deserved it, all of it.
很显然，安妮和我的婚姻出现了些问题
Annie and I were having problems in the marriage, obviously.
你是我唯一的真朋友
You're the only real friend I got.
兄弟，我现在惹上大麻烦了
I'm in trouble, man.
你知道吗？
You know?
关于索尼娅的整件事情 所发生的一切，都让我措手不及
This whole thing with Sonia, what happened, it just snuck up on me.
她是个很了不起的女人
She was an amazing woman,
美丽，风趣，聪明
beautiful and really funny, smart,
而且她，她，很崇拜我
and she, you know, she adored me.
那种感觉非常好，是我从来没有体会过的
That was nice, you know, for a change.
你给她父母打电话了吗？
Have you called the parents?
没有，我没有打给她父母
(SIGHS) No, I haven't called the parents.
你应该打
You should.
明天你打个吊唁电话
Tomorrow, you're gonna make a condolence call.
否则最先引起那些攻击者注意的会是…
The first thing the attack dogs will pick up on, you know,
“我们女儿自杀之后 他甚至连电话都没有打一个”
"He never so much as called after our daughter's suicide."
她不是自杀
She didn't kill herself.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know that?
“嘿，亲爱的，祝你好运 给他们点颜色瞧瞧
Hey, baby, I just want to wish you good luck. I want you to give them hell,
“我很期待周末
and I can't wait for this weekend.
“我爱你，再见”
I love you. Bye.
那是今天早上的
That's this morning.
看上去像一个准备自杀的人吗？
Look like someone who's about to go out and commit suicide?
不像
No.
这个你给其他人看过吗？
You show this to anybody?
是啊，我还想过在YouTube上发布呢
Well, I thought about firing it up on YouTube.
知道吗？
Hey, you know what?
现在我要问你，你到底能愚蠢到什么程度
This is the moment where I ask you how stupid could you be.
这能改变一切
This changes everything.
我们要把一切争取回来
It'll bring it all back your way.
你打算怎么做？
How are you gonna do that?
我们要用事实回击
Because we're gonna fight back with our own facts.
我们所要做的就是编造一个…
All we have to do is, we have to build
合理的故事，明白吗？
a plausible alternative story, all right?
听着
Now, look.
“不幸的是，索尼娅・贝克…
"Unfortunately, it appears that Sonia Baker
“在地铁站台上发生了意外
"has met with a tragic accident on a subway platform.
“所以需要质疑运输安全”
"So questions have to be asked about transit safety."
- 行吗？ - 卡尔
Okay? Cal.
听着，史蒂芬
Now, Stephen,
你必须采取主动，明白吗？
you gotta be proactive, okay?
否则，你就是给那些吸血鬼…
If you're not, then you're just letting the bloodsuckers
和写博客的随意攻击的机会
and the bloggers have another free shot at you.
吸血鬼和写博客的
The bloodsuckers and the bloggers.
你今晚有没有看过环球报的网站？
Have you seen the Globe's website tonight?
没有
No.
“奇耻大辱 - 黛拉・弗雷娅著”
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
喂？
Hello?
国会博客小姐？ 我是卡尔・麦卡弗雷
Miss Capitol Hill Blog? It's Cal McAffrey.
你有笔吗？
Do you have a pen?
什么？
What?
索尼娅・贝克，对吗？
Sonia Baker, right?
我有一个线人，你得和他谈谈
I have a source, and you need to talk to him.
为什么？
Well, why?
你有笔吗？
Do you have a pen?
有
Yeah.
- 莱昂・柯米副队长 - 笔，笔，笔
Lieutenant Leon Comey. Pen, pen, pen.
记下来，C-O-M-E-Y
Write that down. C-O-M-E-Y.
C-O-M-E-Y
C- O-M-E-Y.
202-555-0167
202-555-0167.
他会给你看一份非官方的…
He's gonna show you an off-the-record preview
地铁站监控摄像头拍下的带子
of the security camera tapes from the Metro station.
什么，你是说…你是不是说，现在？
What, you mean... Do you mean, like, now?
是的，现在 不好意思，请问你是？
Yeah, like now. Sorry. Who am I calling?
我找的是叫黛拉・弗雷娅的记者
I was trying to get Della Frye the reporter.
哦，抱歉，我以为我在和今天早晨那个…
Gee, I'm sorry. I thought that I was talking to the guy
不愿和我说话的人讲电话呢
who wouldn't give me the time of day this morning.
听着，我只是想帮助你 好让你下次在网上大放厥词的时候…
Look, I am just trying to help you get a few facts in the mix
至少有一点事实根据
next time you decide to upchuck online.
什么？
What?
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
我才不干，我不干
I'm not doing it. I'm not.
醒醒
DELLA: Wake up.
有人知道514房在哪吗？
Does anybody know where Room 514 is?
514A还是514B？
514A or 514B?
这上面没写，有差吗？
It doesn't say. Is there a big difference?
差别很大，你找的是统一行动组还是调查科？
Big enough. You looking for Uniform Squad or Investigation?
我不知道 卡尔・麦卡弗雷让我来的
I don't know. Cal McAffrey sent me.
为什么不早点说呢？
Why didn't you say so?
你是卡尔的新助手？
You Cal's new assistant?
不，不是
No, I'm not.
嘿，能给我看一下吗？
Hey, can I see that?
沿着走廊到底就是了
Yeah, it's right down the hallway here.
谢谢你
Thank you.
需要警方护送吗？
Like a police escort?
不用了，我没问题 谢谢
No, I'm okay. Thank you.
嘿，没关系的 我吃东西很快
Hey, no trouble. I'm just grabbing some dinner here real quick.
你认识卡尔多久了？
So, how long have you known Cal?
太久了
Too long.
你的职位是什么？ 好的，警官
What's your title? Okay, Sergeant,
我可以申请调查公共档案…
I can file a public records request
然后查到信息
and get the information anyway.
“华盛顿环球报：议员向死去的助手致哀”
你什么都没查到？
You got nothing?
没有
No.
他们有56个摄像头，覆盖了地铁站台
They've got 56 cameras covering the track platforms.
在整个系统中，有3个盲点
There are three blind spots in the entire system,
而索尼娅・贝克就是在其中一个盲点丧命的
and Sonia Baker went down in one of them.
卡尔，你有稿件要交给我吗？
You got copy for me, Cal?
披萨递送员被枪击，你在做什么？
The shooting delivery guy, what are we doing?
我正在写
I'm on it.
我准备让马蒂拍一些受害者家人的照片
Well, I got Marty lined up to take some pictures of the family.
如果需要的话，我可以派人陪他一起去
If you'd like, I can send somebody out there with him.
他可以哭悼，你可以写具体的细节
He can do the crying, you can do the nuts and bolts.
不，不必了，我正在写 今晚交给你
No. No need. I'm on it. You'll have it tonight.
你正在写
You're on it.
好 你知道你必须要做什么吗？
(EXHALING) Okay. You know what you gotta do?
打电话给莱昂，好吗？
Call Leon, all right?
逼他提供些细节
Just sort of push him for the details.
再问他一些问题，就是…
Ask him a few more questions. You know...
20年间有9起自杀事件，有5起意外死亡
Nine suicides in 20 years. There were five accidental deaths,
3起是因为有人在列车进站之前
three from people trying to get their stuff
在轨道上捡东西
off the tracks before the train came
2起是因为精神病患推挤乘客掉入轨道
and two of the psycho-on-stranger pushing attacks.
昨晚柯林斯是不是在你家过夜的？
Did Collins sleep at your place last night?
- 什么？ - 嗯？
What? Hmm?
我只是想确认事实
I was just trying to get my facts straight.
抱歉，我是黛拉
(PHONE RINGING)
Excuse me. Della here.
稍等 他就在这
Yeah, just a sec. He's right here.
等下，等下，等下
Hang on, hang on, hang on.
是安妮・柯林斯的电话
It's Anne Collins.
嘿，我现在不在自己的办公桌旁 能不能一会打给你？
Hey, I'm not at my desk at the moment. Can I call you back?
好的
Yeah.
查一下那两起推挤落轨事件
You know, look into the two psycho-on-stranger cases,
看看有没有联系
see if anything correlates or anything connects.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
(PHONE RINGING)
- 喂？ - 嘿
Hello? CAL... Hey.
- 你还好吗？ - 不
You okay? No.
我的草坪上有很多狗仔队
There are paparazzi on my lawn,
我猜我离上“美国周刊”不远了
so I guess that entitles me to half off on Us Weekly.
我一直试着打你电话
I've been trying to call you.
我关机了
I had my phone off.
你和史蒂芬谈过了吗？
You talk to Stephen yet?
还没
No.
他们要我下去召开记者招待会
They want me to come down for a press conference.
如果你不这么做，他们会把他送上刑场的
Well, you know if you don't, they're gonna toss him on the bonfire.
我并没有很受伤的感觉
You know, I'm not that hurt.
我甚至都不觉得太惊讶
I'm not even that surprised.
只是实在是太丢人了
It's just so humiliating, you know.
(SIGHING)
告诉我你不知道她的存在
Tell me you didn't know about her.
我不知道…
I didn't.
我不知道她，知道吗？
I did not know about her, okay?
我一会乘列车去你那
I'll take the train down.
然后你能不能请我喝酒？
Will you buy me a drink after?
没问题，嘿，给他打个电话，好吗？
Of course. Hey, just call him, all right?
给史蒂芬打个电话
Just call Stephen.
谢谢
Thanks.
德尚・斯塔格
CAL: Deshaun Stagg.
如果他们能把他的名字拼对就好了
Be nice if they could spell his name right.
到现在还没有人来领他的东西
No one's even come to get his stuff yet.
令人发指
It's appalling.
这事从来不会发生在白人身上
Never happen to a white man.
闭嘴 我没那个心情
Skip it. I'm not in the mood.
怎么，不准谈爱，不准谈政治？
What, no love, no politics?
那我们谈什么？
What are we gonna talk about?
我们不谈 你赶紧离开这
We're not. You gotta get out of here
免得我们都惹上麻烦
before we both get into trouble.
他们说只有一个枪手，你怎么认为的？
They're saying it was only one shooter. What do you think?
不清楚
No idea.
毒品呢？
What about drugs?
很有可能
It's a good bet.
得了卡尔 别去碰那堆东西
Come on, Cal, leave that shit alone.
眼睛闭起来，我只是在看他的手机
Close your eyes. I'm just checking out his cell phone.
小心，这个钟点可能正是他们…
(SIGHING) Watch, this will be the moment they decide
来把这些东西取走的时候
to come and pick all this shit up.
那样的话你会怎么办？
Then what are you gonna do?
写些文章，就可以帮我保住饭碗吗？
Write some articles, get me my job back?
你知道我会这么做的
You know I will.
卡尔？
Cal?
卡尔，老天啊 如果杰克进来我怎么向他解释？
Cal, for Christ's sakes, what do I tell Jack if he walks in?
不必解释，因为我搞定了
Nothing, 'cause I'm done.
下次我会给你一个拥抱，好吗？
I'll give you a hug next time, all right?
再见
Bye.
给我买瓶汽水？
Buy me a soda?
不要健怡的
Not diet.
谢谢
Thanks.
(PHONE RINGING)
哟，哟，如果想给基皮留言
Yo, yo, if you want to leave a message for Kippy,
务必留下号码，好吗？
make sure you leave your number, all right?
那样我就你能回打给你，回头见
That way I can call you back. Later for you.
对不起，您所拨打的电话…
AUTOMATED OPERATOR... We're sorry. Your call cannot be...
(PHONE RINGING)
哟，你谁？
MAN... Yo, who this?
我，老兄 你谁？
It's me, man. Who that?
我谁？娘的，是你自己把来电显示屏蔽的！
Me who? Bitch, you the one got your number blocked!
- 不要跟我耍花招，兄弟 - 我是德尚，拜托
Don't be fronting me, man. It's Deshaun. Come on.
- 少来 - 你在哪里？
No. Where you at?
到底是谁给了你我的号码，蠢人？
Who the hell gave you my number, fool?
我刚在和基皮通电话
I was just talking to Kippy.
- 基皮？ - 基皮啊，兄弟
Skippy? Kippy, man.
一点也不好玩，耍花招
This shit ain't funny, trick.
嗨，我是索尼娅・贝克
Hi. You've reached Sonia Baker.
我现在无法接听你的电话
I can't take your call right now,
但是如果你留下姓名和号码
but if you leave your name, number,
以及你打电话的时间 我一定会回打给你，谢谢
and the time you called, I'll be sure to get back to you. Thanks.
嗨，我是索尼娅・贝克
Hi. You've reached Sonia Baker.
我现在无法接听你的电话
I can't take your call right now,
但是如果你留下姓名和号码
but if you leave your name, number,
以及你打电话的时间 我一定会回打给你，谢谢
and the time you called, I'll be sure to get back to you. Thanks.
抱歉
Excuse me.
索尼娅・贝克
Sonia Baker.
我们有关于她吸毒的消息吗？
We got any kind of drug angle on her?
她有被拘捕或者进过戒毒所之类吗？
She ever arrested or rehabbed or anything like that?
- 是谁问的？ - 我
Who's asking? Me.
这报道不是你负责的
You're not on the story.
是我让你去看地铁录像带的，不是吗？
I gave you the Metro tapes idea, right?
没错
Yeah.
你是想把她名声毁坏殆尽吗？
So are you trying to ruin what's left of her reputation?
你这么做是不是为了柯林斯？
Are you doing this for Collins?
一点索尼娅的背景调查？
A little context on Sonia?
你真会开玩笑
You gotta be kidding.
嘿，莫里斯
Hey, Maurice.
嘿，卡尔，和平常一样吗？
Hey, Cal, you getting your regular?
是的
Yeah.
没问题，嘿，小杰！
Sure. Hey, Jay!
一个辣干酪汉堡，一份辣干酪薯条 还有一份辣香肠
I need a chili cheeseburger, a chili cheese fry, and a chili half-smoke.
我正在做汉堡！
I got the burger on!
有人给你点单了吗？
Anybody get you yet?
“本氏餐馆免费就餐名单： 只有比尔・科斯比”
好的 你饿了，对吗？
All right. You're a hungry man, eh?
是的
Yeah.
情况怎么样，黑皮？
How's it going, Happy?
想再要一瓶汽水的话，大可不必这样做
That's a long way to go for another soda.
你想买德尚最后一次偷的包里的东西吗？
You want to buy something from the last bag Deshaun ever stole?
我需要500美元
I need 500 bucks.
你上火车的时候安全吗？
Did you get the train okay?
什么？
What?
你上火车的时候安全吗？
Did you get on the train all right?
一路上，一切都好吗？
Get through. Everything okay?
你想在这聊天吗？
You're gonna make small talk?
我去看看安排的怎样了
(CLEARING THROAT) I will go check on the arrangements.
对不起
I'm sorry.
声明不用很详细的
It doesn't have to be a detailed statement.
简单而庄重，我们就可以离开了
Short and dignified, and we'll be out of here.
庄重，明白了
Dignified. Got it.
女士们，先生们 感谢你们今天的到来
MAN... Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for joining us here today.
柯林斯先生和太太会发表简短声明
Mr. And Mrs. Collins would like to give you a brief statement.
德尚是从星巴克咖啡馆的一个男人…
GIRL: Deshaun boosted this metal briefcase
男人那偷来这个铁皮公文包的
from some guy outside of Starbucks.
那就是我们的活
That's what we did, you know?
偷别人的包然后再卖给他
Grab a guy's bag and sell it back to him.
通常包里只装些商业文件和其他东西
Usually we just got, like, people's business papers and shit.
而这个？ 这个不一样
This one? This one was different.
包里还有一把枪
GIRL: There was a gun in there, too,
还有一小包看上去很奇怪的子弹
and a little bag of these weird-looking bullets.
你看到过这个包的主人吗？
Did you see the guy that owned the bag?
没有
No.
我告诉过德尚不应该把这包卖回去的
I told Deshaun we shouldn't sell this bag back.
我想那女人该怎么办？
I mean, you know, what about the girl?
但是他毒瘾上来了
But he needed a fix real bad,
于是就和这个人商定了时间和地点
and he and this guy figured out a time and place.
然后就是这样子
And that was it.
他一去不复返
My boy never came back.
你事先把这些从公文包里拿了出来
You took these out of the briefcase first,
然后你用德尚的手机给她打了电话
and then you called her from Deshaun's phone.
她的号码也在文件里
Her number was there, too.
我认为她有必要知道
I figured someone had to warn her
有个变态在跟踪她
that this psycho was following her around.
只是她没有接电话
She just didn't pick up.
柯林斯先生采取行动…
Mr. Collins moved to staunch a growing tide
来控制日渐增长的反对呼声
of hostility towards him this afternoon
他于今日下午现身，携同…
when he appeared together with his...
…世代都嫁给了政客
... the long line of politicians' wives.
我们有过成功，也有过失败
We've had triumphs and disappointments,
我们俩都犯过错误以致于…
and we've both made mistakes that have caused...
要为他的婚外情道歉，向他的宣选民道歉
MAN... apologize for his affair and offer an apology to his constituents.
你能相信吗？
Can you believe this?
有六个台同时在播我们的声明
We're on six channels simultaneously.
卡尔…有谁会希望索尼娅死？
CAL... Who might have wanted Sonia dead?
- 什么？ - 关于她的过去…
What? Is there something in her history,
你是否对我有所隐瞒？
you know, something you haven't told me about?
像是一些令她深陷泥潭的关系？
Some connections that might have got her in trouble?
不，没有，没有，等一下，我这是…
No. No, no. Wait, who...
我是在和我的朋友说话…
Am I talking to my friend now,
还是和一个记者？
or am I talking to a reporter?
两者都是
I gotta be both.
你听说过一个叫德尚・斯塔格的人吗？
You ever heard of a guy called Deshaun Stagg?
没有
No.
是个小毛孩，街头毛贼
Was a kid. Minor criminal.
嗜毒，索尼娅死的前一晚被枪杀了
Drug addict. Got shot and killed the night before Sonia died.
卡尔，索尼娅从来不吸毒
Cal, Sonia didn't have anything to do with drugs.
听着，史蒂芬，这些事情…
Look, Stephen, I'm telling you things
我还没有和报社谈过
that I haven't even discussed with the paper.
好吗，你要好好想想
Okay, you gotta think about this.
谁有可能想置索尼娅于死地？
Who might have wanted Sonia dead?
这个男人在每张她哭泣的照片中都出现 他是谁？
CHRIS: Who is this man here in all the photographs where she's crying?
我们还不清楚
CAL: We don't know that yet.
她在和柯林斯共事之前是做什么的？
And what was her background before she started working with Collins?
从她的简历上看，很乱
DELLA: Well, she has some very random moments in her résumé.
她曾经… 她做过几份服务员的工作
She was... She waitressed a couple times.
她有许多坏账
She had a string of bad debts.
两年前入店行窃被叛罪
Shoplifting conviction two years ago.
国会难道不调查雇员背景吗？
Don't they do background checks on the Hill?
她替柯林斯写了有关银行规范…
DELLA: She wrote position papers for Collins
和证券交易委员会的意见书
about bank regulations and the SEC.
很多人都觉得她很有才华
I mean, a lot of people thought she was a star.
同时她还是针对“尖兵集团”的听证会的 首席研究员
She was also the lead researcher on the PointCorp hearings.
那又怎样？
CAMERON: So?
史蒂芬会让那些人损失很多钱
Stephen represents the loss of a lot of money for those guys.
听着，如果这些一切只是…
Look, what if all of this is just an attempt
为了排挤史蒂芬・柯林斯，会怎样？
to marginalize Stephen Collins?
你能说出这样的话，一定很爱他，对吧？
CAMERON: You've gotta love him for it, haven't you?
给他24小时和一具小巷里的尸体
I mean, you give him 24 hours, body in the alley,
这个老头就能编出一个…
and this geezer will turn it into
有模有样的集团阴谋
a full-blown corporate conspiracy.
你看不到关联吗？
You don't see any connection?
看不到
No.
那好吧，我们现在整理一下我们知道的情报 好吗？
All right. Let's go through what we know, okay?
那个尾随索尼娅・贝克的男人
The guy that was stalking Sonia Baker,
枪杀了德尚・斯塔格 和弗农・桑杜
he shot Deshaun Stagg and Vernon Sando.
德尚・斯塔格没有固定居所 他偷了一个文件包
Deshaun Stagg, of no fixed abode, he boosts a briefcase.
那个文件包里装着这些照片
Now, in that briefcase are these photographs,
据知线人所说 还装着一小包奇怪的子弹
and according to our source, a little baggie of weird bullets.
地铁警局的弹道分析结果显示
Metro PD ballistics tell me
犯罪现场的弹壳是被二次使用的 我们无法追踪
the casings at the crime scene were reloads, untraceable.
子弹比普通商店里买的重两倍， 是手动发射的
The slugs were hand cast at twice the weight of store-bought bullets,
是扩散型的
X'ed for expansion.
也就是说杀手想置人于死地
So that means that the shooter intended to kill.
斯塔格和桑杜都连挨两枪
Stagg and Sando were both double-tapped,
一颗子弹在脊椎，另一颗在头部 这是职业杀手的做法
one bullet in the spine, one in the head. That is the mark of a pro,
或者至少也是当过兵的
or at the very least, somebody with a military background,
甚至有可能是特种部队的
perhaps even Special Forces.
“尖兵集团”的建立者和雇员 全都是当过兵的人
PointCorp founded by, staffed by 100./. Ex-military.
我觉得这是我们不能忽视的关联
I think that's a connection we can't ignore.
克里斯，我们最迟什么时候移交证据？
Chris, how long before we have to hand these over?
确认，查询相关的档案…
CHRIS: Time to verify, consult relevant case files,
外部法律顾问 加起来最多48小时
outside counsel, 48 hours, tops.
但如果这就是证据 不应该现在就给他警方吗？
But if this is evidence, don't they need to see it now?
他怎么样了？
How's he doing?
嘿，如果要确认身份，你会通知我的 对吗？
Hey, you gonna let me know if I gotta call the ID team, right?
我会通知你的
NURSE: I'll let you know.
沃特・什洛亚，你那好色的朋友的战友…
Walter Schroyer, Army buddy of your libidinous friend,
在那篇蹩脚的文章里对史蒂芬・柯林斯
gives his moving tribute to Stephen Collins
进行了高度的赞扬，为什么不是我们？
in that asswipe excuse of a paper and not to us. Why?
史蒂芬・柯林斯是那种你想
CAL: Platitudes, padding and fluff.
陈词滥调 都是充字数的
我是记者，不是广告员
I'm a journalist. I'm not a publicist.
我想再叫些人…
CAMERON: I want to bring some more people in
和你一起工作，卡尔
to work with you on this, Cal,
写政治新闻的，有实战经验的人
on the political side, people with real experience.
我在考虑泰德・穆迪
I'm thinking Ted Moody.
泰德再合适不过了
I mean, Ted's perfect for this.
你不想让我插手了吗？
Are you taking me off the story?
不，不是 不是不插手，只是做二线
No, no. Not off, just off point.
如果这件事情真像他说过的那样 “如果”是真的
If this is as big as he says it is, a big "if,"
那么这对你来说是有好处的
then it's gonna be good for you.
那，那有什么好的？
How? How is that good?
观察资深记者…
Well, watching seasoned reporters
调查新闻
that work on a big story, you know,
并且参与其中，你会学到很多东西的
being a part of it all, you'll learn a lot.
泰德・穆迪，你意下如何？
So, Ted Moody, what do you think?
不要让她插手
Don't let her do it.
卡尔，你要调查的话 我希望你不要被私人关系束缚
And, Cal, if you're on this, I want this to be clean through and through.
跟她说别想了 这是你的舞会
Tell her to forget it. It's your gig.
你能行的，欢呼吧
You got it. Get loud now.
不好意思，你现在是在替她说话吗？
Excuse me. You're defending her now?
她很好，我可以和她共事
She's fine. I can work with her.
但是，卡尔，她没有经验
But, Cal, she's inexperienced.
没有经验不要紧
Inexperience isn't fatal.
我不会半途而废的！
I'm not giving up the story!
我…对不起，我只是…
I just... Sorry. I just...
再给我几天时间
If I could just have a few more days with it,
我保证不会让你失望
I promise you I'm not gonna let you down.
看在上帝份上
For Christ's sake.
不要像个新人记者那样泪汪汪的看着我
Don't throw those dewy cub reporter eyes at me.
有点恶心
It's nauseating.
谢你全家
And fuck you very much.
不客气
Pleasure.
这是丽芙护士和我… 化验结果出来了
This is Nurse Leif and myself... The lab work's back.
是你要求的13小组？
It's the panel 13 you ordered?
我们半小时之前就打电话给神经科医师了
Yeah, well, we called for a neurologist a half hour ago.
先生，你不能在这里用手机
You can't use that phone here, sir.
嘿，什么事，卡恩斯？ 你怎么样？
Hey. What's up, Carnes? How you doing?
没错，没错
Yeah. Yeah.
那个叫桑杜的人似乎快醒了
Looks like that Sando guy's waking up.
你要派人过来吗？
You sending anyone over?
你以前去过华盛顿医院吗？
You ever been to D.C. Hospital?
没有
No.
别担心，很简单的
Don't worry about it. It's easy.
三楼重症监护室那有一个穿制服的警察
CAL: All right, there's a uniformed officer on the third floor ICU.
- 好的 - 记下来，有笔吗？
Okay. Write it down. Got a pen?
- 有的 - 给
Yes. Here.
- 我有笔的 - 好的
I have a pen. Okay.
那个穿制服的警察叫布朗
The uniformed officer's name is Brown.
- 记下了吗？ - 布朗
Okay. Brown.
三楼重症监护室 告诉他拜恩斯探员…
Third floor ICU. Tell him that Detective Bynes,
B-Y-N-E-S，乔・拜恩斯…
B-Y-N-E-S, Joe Bynes...
好的
Okay.
好了，拜恩斯让你通行的
All right, he cleared you for access.
通行去哪里？
Access for what?
弗农・桑杜，卖批萨的那个人 似乎他快醒了
Vernon Sando, the pizza guy, looks like he's coming around.
那是你负责的部分
That's your side of the story.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
你听到我说的了
You heard me.
你要我坐在医院里…
You want me to go and sit around in some hospital,
等一个有可能从昏迷中苏醒的人
waiting for a guy who looks like he might be coming out of a coma,
而你就可以把其他部分都清理掉？
while you clean up the rest of the story?
我说，你所有的目的就是这个？
I mean, is that what that was all about in there?
听着，这是真实事件
Look, this is a real story.
真相只有一个
It's not open for interpretation.
不能妄加猜测
It does not require opinion.
两具尸体，还有一个人昏迷
We got two dead bodies, and we got a guy in a coma,
而我们先人一步掌握一条线索
and we got us with a lead that nobody else has got.
我们必须作出决定
So you gotta make a decision,
因为今晚我还要追踪另一条线索
because I have to follow another lead tonight,
而我不会分身术
and I cannot be in two places at one time.
所以，你今天晚上将就一下守在医院
So, are you gonna be okay slumming it
看看弗农・桑杜会不会醒过来，行吗？
to find out if Vernon Sando's coming around or not?
好的
Good.
如果我们要共事的话，我们就必须合作
If we're gonna work together, we gotta work together.
好吗？说定了？
Yeah? Deal?
好了，一会见
All right, see you later.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
抱歉
Excuse me.
别跟我说你还找不到路
Don't tell me you're still lost.
嘿，你在这干什么？
Hey, what are you doing here?
工作
Working.
你是布朗警官？
You're Officer Brown?
你就是我要找的人
You're who I'm looking for.
我知道你会回来的
(CHUCKLING) I knew you'd come around.
桑杜怎么样了？ 他醒了吗？
(CELL PHONE RINGING) How about Sando? Is he coming around?
是，是的，看上去快醒了
Yeah, yeah, it looks that way.
他们现在派了一个警探过来
They're sending a detective over right now.
也需要确认一下身份
Maybe get an ID.
真的？
Really?
这电话我得接
I gotta take this.
哦，接吧
Yeah, go ahead.
我是布朗警官
Yeah, Officer Brown.
没有，先生
No, sir.
你好吗？
You okay?
我爸爸曾经劝过我要小心政客
My dad did warn me about politicians.
比起政客，他更讨厌记者
The only people he hated more was journalists.
他很明智
Smart man.
我让你紧张了
I'm making you nervous.
你一向如此
You always did.
有人说性是友谊的克星
Well, they say sex is the best way to ruin a friendship.
有人这么说？ 是谁？
They do, do they? And who's they?
大都会杂志？青春悸动？
What, Cosmopolitan magazine? Teen Beat?
得了
Come on.
告诉我，我们的友谊没有被性影响
Tell me, please, it didn't ruin ours.
完好如初
It hasn't ruined anything.
脉搏82
NURSE: Pulse is 82.
血压105-79， 血饱和氧量94
BP is 105 over 79, O2 sats 94.
情况稳定
He seems stable.
好的，我们再检查一次血液，全面血检…
DOCTOR: Okay, let's do another blood work-up, CBCs...
- 小姐，你不能呆在这 - 我只是想…
Miss, you cannot be in here. I'd just like to
- 问他一些问题 - 小姐，请吧
ask him a couple of questions. DOCTOR: Miss, please!
- 不，我很抱歉 - 拜托，听着
No, I'm sorry. Come on. Look.
你不应该进来的
You know you're not supposed to be in here.
我知道，我只是…
I know. I just...
趴下！
(SCREAMING) Get on the ground!
退后！趴着
OFFICER BROWN: Stand back! Stay down.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
是我同事，我得走了
That's a colleague of mine. I'm gonna have to go.
很抱歉，改天见
I'm really sorry. I'll see you soon.
好的
Okay.
(SIRENS WAILING)
让他进来，让他进来
OFFICER: Let him through. Blockade, let him through.
嘿，瑞奇！
Hey, Ricky!
让他进来
Let him through.
黛拉！
Della!
你还好吗？ 你没事吧？
You okay? You all right?
- 黛拉，告诉这不是你的，对吗？ - 什么东西？
Della, tell me that's not yours, right? What is it?
只是一点血
It's just a little bit of blood.
没事，有我在，有我在，有我在
It's all right. I got it, I got it, I got it.
没事了
It's okay.
(WHIMPERING)
没事了，好了，好了
(CRYING)
It's all right. It's all right. It's all right.
哦，我的天，卡尔 我们本来能救他的！
Oh, my God, Cal, we could have stopped this!
怎么救，利用灵媒？
What, by being psychic?
不，我们应该把那份文件交给警方的
No. We should have given the police that file.
说不定照片上有指纹呢？
What if there were fingerprints on the photographs?
天啊，卡尔，我们不能坐视不管
God, Cal, we can't just let people get hurt like that.
听着，都结束了，没事了，没事了
Look, it's over. It's all right. It's okay.
我们不能见死不救
We can't just keep letting people get killed.
不，有关系
No, it's not okay.
没关系了，都过去了，都结束了
It's okay. It's over. It's over.
已经结束了
It's over.
明白吗？没事了
All right? It's okay.
你们搁置了杀人案件的证据
CHRIS: You're sitting on evidence in an execution homicide.
你们觉得昨晚受害者的家人…
How do you think that's gonna play with the family of the guy
要是知道了会有什么反应？
that just got shot last night?
克里斯，事情已经过去了
Chris, let's be productive.
等等，我还没有说完
Hold on, I'm actually not done.
我们的记者昨天晚上已经向警方提交了供述
Our reporter made a full statement last night.
什么，什么时候的事情？
CHRIS: What, you had these when?
卡姆，不要告诉他
Cam, don't answer that!
什么时候发生的事？ 你想要被传审吗？
When did you have these? You want subpoenas?
我现在就去打电话
I'll get on the phone right now.
我们给你打电话了！ 在打给外部法律顾问之前！
We called you! We called you before we called outside counsel.
有点晚，有一点晚
A little late. It's a little late.
得了吧
Give me a break.
最近好吗，唐？
How you doing, Don?
我还说得过去，卡尔，你呢？
I'm hanging in, Cal. You?
很好，我很好
Good. Good.
还有其他线索需要我处理吗？
This source have anything else I might need to do my job?
等一下
Wait a minute.
没有了，好吗？就这些了
Nothing, all right? This was it,
我们知道了也不到一天
and we've kept it for less than a day.
警探，我们也是直到昨天晚上才知道 事情的严重性的
Detective, until last night, we didn't actually know what we had here.
胡说
Bullshit.
你以为我是谁？傻子吗？
DONALD: Who do you think I am, Bambi's baby brother?
不是的，先生
No, sir.
你很清楚这份证据的分量
You knew exactly what you had.
只是你觉得你比我们更需要这份证据
You just decided that your need was greater than ours,
现在你手上沾满了血腥
and now you have blood on your hands.
等等
CAL: Hold on.
警探先生，听着
CAMERON: Detective, look.
我们正在筹备的文章
The thesis that we are pursuing
涉及了国会议员柯林斯先生正在调查的 一家公司
involves a certain company that Congressman Collins is investigating.
这是集团阴谋？
DONALD: What, this is corporate conspiracies
并且直接威胁最高领导层？
that threaten the highest levels?
我做了这么多年的警探 只在电视上看到过这类事情
All my years on the job, I've only ever seen that on TV.
我认识你那么多年，你只看体育比赛
All the years I've known you, you've only ever watched sports on TV.
警探先生，我们与您合作
CAMERON: So, Detective, in exchange for our cooperation,
请问您能否也坦诚相待呢？
can we be assured that you will open your books to us?
作为回报？
Quid pro quo?
如果我们决定将证据公诸于众 会提前6小时通知你们的
If we decide to go public with this, we'll give you six hours,
但是仅此而已
but that's the end of it.
这起蓄意杀人案的调查是公开的
This is an open homicide investigation.
你们拖我们后腿，将公众置于危险境地
You slow us down, endanger the public
如果再有类似情况的话
any more than you already have,
就不会这么简单了
it won't be pretty.
正式申明一下，对于你们…
For the record, I'm still not happy
上交证据的方式，我还是很不开心
the way you presented the evidence.
我要把我的感觉说出来
I'm just gonna put that out there.
别管和警方的闲扯
CAMERON: Police gossip being what it is,
我猜想甚至“今夜娱乐”节目…
I'm guessing that even Entertainment Tonight
在48小时内了解的情况不会比我们少
will know as much as we do within 48 hours.
所以我们今天必须有确凿的报道
So we've gotta have something solid today.
也就是说不要猜想，不要匿名信息
That means no assumptions, no unnamed sources.
我需要翔实的报道 我要这件事情水落石出
Not fast and loose. I want this thing wrung out.
如果我们输给警察的话，那就太丢人了
Damned if we can't do a better job of it than those cops.
黛拉，你还好吗？
Della, how are you?
我很好
I'm good.
- 真的？ - 嗯
Yeah? Mmm-hmm.
好，好的
Good, okay.
你负责索尼娅・贝克，好吗？
Well, you take Sonia Baker, okay?
我要尽可能多的关于她的信息
I want to know everything that we can about her,
她认识谁，和谁有性关系，内裤的颜色
who she knew, who she blew, the color of her knickers.
- 明白了 - “尖兵集团”？
Got it. PointCorp?
好，汉克和皮特 你们和卡尔一起负责
Okay. Hank and Pete, you work with Cal.
好
Cool.
你们要谨慎
The rule on this one is discretion.
在“独眼”喝酒时可不应该讨论这个问题
This is not a good subject for gossip over drinks at the Monocle,
还有你，在文件柜吸大麻的时候也不许
or spliffs in the stationery cupboard, you.
我觉得被冒犯了，真的
I'm offended, truly.
生气吧
CAMERON: Well, be offended.
下楼，收拾东西，带到这来
Go downstairs, get your stuff, bring it in here,
这就是你的新家了
because this is your new home.
去啊！
Go on!
好！ 行行行 光速
Okay! Yes, yes, yes. Speed of light.
卡尔？对你来说有利益冲突吗？
Cal? Any conflict of interest here?
没有
No.
也许这是一个很好的机会…
SLATOFF... Perhaps this is a good opportunity
来处理另一个在这些听证会中…
to address another issue that's been discussed
备受关注的问题，价格结构
during these hearings, your price structure.
当然，谢谢您给我这次机会…
Surely, and I thank you for giving me
来讨论这个问题
an opportunity to touch on that today.
我公司的价格结构遵循国防部…
Our price structure follows the Defense Department model
在第一次海湾战争期间建立的模式
as established in the first Gulf War,
当然，由于通货膨胀做了相应调整
adjusted, of course, for inflation.
令人欣慰的是，这次的大额支出是因为…
Happily, what's costing us so much this time around
我们在战地医疗方面取得了长足的进步
are some incredible advances in on-field medical care.
但是，简单来说，我们现在保持更多的…
But, simply, we're now keeping more...
先生，抱歉，只是…
Sir, I'm sorry. Just...
在您当兵的时候，您打过仗吗？
When you were in the military, did you see any combat duty?
没有，先生，我没有，没有
No, sir, I did not. No.
如果你打过仗，你觉得会改变你的看法吗？
Do you think if you had, you might see things differently?
我们都知道您参加过战争，议员
MAN... We're all aware of your war record, Congressman.
我说的不是我
STEPHEN... I'm not talking about my record.
我指的是对“尖兵集团”以及分包商…
I'm talking about the numerous allegations of atrocities
对伊拉克和阿富汗平民…
committed by PointCorp and its subsidiary contractors
所犯下的累累罪行的控诉
against the civilian population in Iraq and Afghanistan.
那些指控没有确凿证据
MAN... Those are unsubstantiated allegations.
好的 那我直说了
Okay. This is straightforward.
自从反恐战争开始后…
Since a war on terror was declared,
您的身价是否上升了两亿五千万美元？
has your personal net worth gone up by more than $250 million?
直接的问题
Straightforward question.
抱歉，据说在公开会议中…
Excuse me, I was told that personal financial data
个人经济状况是不予讨论的
would not be addressed in open session.
适应情况
Adapt.
那不正是你们的宣传语吗？
Isn't that your slogan?
“适应情况，争取成功”
"Adapt and Achieve?"
这本宣传册上是这么写的
It's on the brochure here.
“Commoda et Confice” 你们是用拉丁文写的
"Commoda et Confice." You have it in Latin.
您的意思是？
MAN... Your point being?
将战争交由惟利是图的人…
Putting war in the hands of mercenaries
以及把战争看做是商机的人掌控
and those who consider it a business
无论在任何语言中，都是矛盾的
is a contradiction in terms in any language.
我能否提醒你，先生
May I remind you, sir, that the wars
这个国家所参加的影响历史的战争
this country fought, that defined it,
不是以金钱来计算的，更不是为了金钱而战
were fought despite what they cost, not because of it.
我来这不是受道德教育的，议员先生
I didn't come here for a lesson in morality, Congressman.
是的，我想也是的
No, I expect you didn't.
尤其不是从你这受教育
Well, especially from you.
为“尖兵集团”工作的人
The men who work for PointCorp,
那些被你贬低成惟利是图的人
the men you dishonor by calling them mercenaries
大部分都是退役美国军人
are, by and large, retired American military personnel.
这体系很完善，对吗？
It's a great system, isn't it?
我们出钱训练军人，然后你们送他们上战场 自己发财
We pay to train these men, and you get rich by killing them.
(CROWD MURMURING)
“尖兵集团”运转的很好
PETE... PointCorp, well, they're on a roll.
他们刚买了60，000英亩的土地 扩建设备
They just bought 60,000 acres to expand their facility.
- 60,000英亩 - 没错
60,000 acres. Yeah.
在哪？
Where?
北卡罗来纳州的康维
In Conway, North Carolina.
当地人称之为小巴格达
The locals call it Little Baghdad.
但是并不小
Not so little.
他们在当地还有些房地产生意
HANK... They've also got some interesting real estate locally.
在水门大厦有办公室
Offices at the Watergate building.
看看
Check that out.
“自由倡议勋章” 是什么？
"Medal of Freedom Initiative." What's that?
议员游说者行业
PETE... It's a lobbying interest.
是的，根据网站内容
HANK... Yeah, according to the website,
MOFI，自由倡议勋章
MOFI, Medal of Freedom Initiative,
是一部分私营防卫承包商…
is an umbrella group for a bunch
的保护伞组织
of these private defense contractors.
他们游说些议员，开些舞会 抹杀些事情
You know, they lobby a little, party a little, kill things.
MOFI！
PETE... MOFI!
有人吗？
(WHOOPING)
Hello?
我们去过那里了，一个人都没有
PETE... We went down there. The place is totally empty...
就好像他们在等待征新兵一样
Like they're just waiting for all their new recruits.
他们外派到到孟买还是怎么了？
Did they outsource to Mumbai or something?
还是在等待壮大队伍？
Or are they just getting ready for an expansion?
有人吗？
CAL: Hello?
我是黛拉・弗雷娅，我是环球报的记者
This is Della Frye. I'm a reporter over at the Globe.
你曾经是索尼娅・贝克的律师
You were Sonia Baker's attorney
负责她入店行窃的案件，对吗？
on her shoplifting case, correct?
是不是多米尼克把我的号码给你的？
MAN... Did Dominic give you my number?
没错，你是怎么认识多米尼克的？
Yes, how do you know Dominic?
我很抱歉，这样做不太合适
Well, I'm sorry. This really isn't appropriate.
我…
(LINE DISCONNECTS) I...
嘿，麦克，我想找个人…
Hey, Michael, I need someone to help me dig
深入了解“尖兵集团”
a little deeper into PointCorp.
我需要一个公司内部人员
I need somebody on the inside,
并且要知道他们是如何运转的
somebody who knows the way they operate.
她到处欠债
WOMAN... She owed everybody money.
哦，天啊，所以她才穿着内衣…
Oh, God, that's how she always walked around,
到处跑
in her underwear.
太好了！ 你动了，你不能动的
Yeah! You moved. You can't move.
嗨！你好！是的，是的
Hi! Hi, yes, yes.
这是谁？ 看着有点眼熟
Who is this? He looks familiar.
多米尼克・弗伊 索尼娅的朋友
WOMAN: Dominic Foy. He's a friend of Sonia's.
多米尼克
Dominic.
嘿，麦克，是卡尔 你发现了什么？
Hey, Michael, it's Cal. So what did you find out?
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
你好，斯塔勒先生？ 什么事？
DELLA... Hi. Mr. Statler? STATLER... Yes?
我是环球报的记者
Yes, I'm from the Globe.
我在写一篇关于索尼娅・贝克之死的文章
I'm writing an article on the death of Sonia Baker,
我想…
and I just wanted to...
他曾在“尖兵集团”当高层？
And he was, like, high up in PointCorp?
你好，我是华盛顿环球报的黛拉・弗雷娅
Hi. Della Frye from the Washington Globe.
我…我能不能和你谈谈？ 请别…
I... Could I speak to you? Please don't...
是的，我还没挂 因为我就是干这个的，我喜欢这么做
Yes, I'm still holding 'cause that's what I do. That's what I like to do.
索尼娅・贝克以前的舍友 朗达・希瓦
Sonia Baker's ex-roommate, Rhonda Silver.
没有人知道她在哪
Nobody's got her yet.
在过去的几年里她换了很多名字
She changed her name a couple times in the past year.
你怎么知道的？
How'd you get it?
我答应了和一个很会出汗的叫维克的人约会
I had to agree to go on not one,
不是一次，而是两次约会
but two dates with a sweaty guy named Vic.
千万别问
Don't even ask me.
嘿，鲍勃，是卡尔
Hey, Bob, it's Cal.
能不能帮我查一个社保号码？
Want to run a Social Security number for me?
“‘尖兵集团’经理深陷政府直派合同”
“‘尖兵集团’拒绝公布伤亡数字”
朗达・希瓦的号码
(EXCLAIMS)
Rhonda Silver's number.
我们刚才那么做犯法吗？
Did we just break the law?
没，我们称之为精确报道
Nope, that's what you call damn fine reporting.
- 你的笔 - 留着吧
Your pen. Keep it.
- 不用谢！ - 谢谢！
You're welcome! Thank you!
嗨，请问朗达在吗？
Hi. Is Rhonda there, please?
我是朗达的旧校友
I'm actually an old friend of Rhonda's from school.
我今天正好在这，我想去看看她
I'm in town for the day, and I thought maybe I'd stop by and see her.
我可以去她工作单位吗？
Do you think I could show up at her work?
那样可以吗？
Would that be all right?
先生，我一会再打给你，行吗？
Actually, sir, can I call you back?
那一页和下页
That page and the next page.
这个叫杰瑞・塞姆斯的是当地的政客
HANK: This guy, Jerry Symes, local politician,
他参加了反扩张运动…
he campaigns against the expansion,
接着就在一起离奇的车祸中丧生
and then he dies in a freak car accident.
好的，“离奇的车祸”是什么意思？
CAL: All right, what does "freak car accident" mean?
大白天…他在空旷的马路上开车
Middle of the day... He's driving on the open road...
- 没有目击证人 - …30英里时速…
No witnesses. ...30 miles an hour...
- 天气很好，没有打滑的痕迹 - …汽车翻了身
Perfect weather, no skid marks. ...car turns over.
警方认为有可能是睡眠中呼吸中断
And the police think it might be sleep apnea.
卡尔，抱歉，我有重要的事情要和你说
Cal. Sorry, I really need to talk to you.
发现什么了？
What do you got?
我刚在看那段有索尼娅…
So, I was looking for images of Sonia
的地铁监视录像
in the Metro security footage, right?
她进入盲点20分钟后，这个人出现了
And 20 seconds after she went into the blind spot, this guy appears.
知道吗？
Okay?
我昨晚在医院看到他了
I think that I saw him last night at the hospital.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
麦克，我是卡尔
Michael, it's Cal.
你说的“尖兵集团”的内部人员 我现在要见他
Your PointCorp insider, I need to meet him, now.
你要知道
I want you to know something.
我爱祖国
I love my country.
我爱军队
I love the military.
我的目标是挽救他们
My aim here is to save them.
你明白我的规矩吗？
You understand my terms?
我不会告诉你名字
I will not give you my name.
也不会告诉你我在“尖兵集团”的职位
I will not give you my rank in the PointCorp military structure,
以及我服役的起讫日期
or the in and out dates of my service.
明白了
Understand.
我在找一个人
CAL: I'm looking for a guy that PointCorp
他参加了“尖兵集团”的隐蔽军事行动
are using on a covert operation.
官方完全否认
Total deniability.
我们在国防部共同的朋友觉得…
Our mutual friend at DOD thought
你有可能能帮助我们找到他
you might be able to help us find him.
我不知道，我会查一下
I don't know. I'll check it out.
你是怎么理解“尖兵集团”的口号的？
So, what's your understanding of the PointCorp MO?
他们的口号？
Their MO?
他们随心所欲
They do whatever the hell they want.
这些军人不受束缚
These soldiers are answerable to no one.
只对支票效忠
They're loyal to nothing but a paycheck.
是对穆斯林恐怖主义的淘金热
It's the Muslim terror gold rush.
- 那些听证会你注意没？ - 是的
You've been watching these hearings? Yeah.
委员会的主席，史蒂芬・柯林斯…
So, the head of the committee there, Stephen Collins...
他完蛋了
He's finished.
他们会不断攻击他直到他离职
They'll just keep knocking him down until he goes away.
你知道他的所做所为造成了多大的威胁吗？
Do you have any idea what he's threatening here?
公司每年赚三、四百亿
This is $30 or $40 billion annually.
上帝都会愤怒的数字
That's wrath of God money.
听证会上说的是三、四十亿
The hearings are saying 3 or 4.
那是海外的，真正让尖兵集团赚大钱的…
Overseas. The real money is what PointCorp
是国内的军事行动
stands to make in its domestic operations.
我以为他们不在国内行动
I wasn't aware that they had any.
卡特里娜飓风过后是谁被派去控制局面？ 是我们
Who was sent in for crowd control after Hurricane Katrina? Us.
私营安保承包商被授权…
Private security contractors deputized
射击美国民众
to shoot at American citizens.
芝加哥警察的新审问技巧是谁训练出来的？
Who's training Chicago police on new interrogation techniques?
很快，“尖兵集团”就会取代国家安全委员会
Soon, PointCorp will take over from the NSA
监听电话，有关恐怖分子资料，所有的一切
on phone taps, terrorist databases, all of it.
这是国内情报策略的…
It's a fundamental restructuring
根本重组
of domestic intelligence policy.
是国土安全的民营私有化
It is the privatization of Homeland Security.
数以亿计的美元
Billions and billions of dollars.
你真的认为他们会为了一个…
Now you really think they're gonna forfeit all that
从宾夕法尼亚州第七选区来的英雄…
because some hero from the seventh district
放弃所有这一切吗？
of Pennsylvania thinks that they should?
嘿
Hey.
我刚联系到了一个曾经在 “尖兵集团”工作的员工
CAL... I just got told by a former PointCorp employee
他告诉我他们打算垄断国家安全工作
that they have a plan to monopolize domestic security
每年可赚四百亿
that's worth about $40 billion a year.
是真的吗？
Is that true?
- 没错 - 怎么做的？
STEPHEN... Yes. CAL... How?
你不能把所有我告诉你的事情与我关联起来
You cannot connect anything that I tell you back to me.
- 你知道吗？ - 当然
You understand? Of course.
好吧
Okay.
去年有47家公司竞标国土安全合约
Last year, 47 companies bid on major Homeland Security contracts.
其中有16家公司夺标
Of those, 16 companies were granted the bids.
在夺标的公司中，14家公司有联系
Of those, I could make connections between 14 companies,
我说的不是…
and I'm not just talking about someone leaving one company
公司间的人员流动
and go work for another.
我说的是共同的银行帐户
I'm talking about shared banking practices.
说的是一致的阴谋
I'm talking about collusive behavior.
我的观点就是 到最后…
Now, my belief is, when all's said and done
把面纱揭开…
and when the veil is pulled away,
你看到的不是14家不同的公司
you will not see 14 individual companies.
而是一家公司，明白吗?
You will see one company. You understand?
你一直在四处打探
And you've been digging around
试图弄清他们之间的关系
trying to make those connections clear.
是的，没错
Yeah. That's right.
索尼娅也参与其中？
And Sonia was working on that?
她是首席研究员
She was my lead researcher.
她参与了所有事情
She was involved in everything we did.
他们无论如何不会放过你的，史蒂芬
They're gonna get you, Stephen, one way or another.
他们有四百亿个好理由除掉你
They got 40 billion good reasons to want you out of the way.
你必须发表正式申明
You gotta go on the record.
将焦点转向他们
Swing the spotlight back on them.
你得保护自己，兄弟
You gotta protect yourself, man.
你要帮我找能把索尼娅的死和“尖兵集团”…
You go out there and find me evidence
联系起来的证据
linking Sonia's death to PointCorp.
我会发表正式申明
I will go on the record.
我会将这件事公诸于众
I will shout this thing from the rooftops.
我没问题
I can do that.
好了，我要进去了，保持联系
All right. I gotta get back. I'll be in touch.
- 史蒂芬 - 什么事？
Stephen. Yeah?
一切小心
Just watch your back.
你也是
You, too.
嗨，朗达在这吗？
Hi. Is Rhonda here?
在，她就在那边
Yeah, she's just right over there.
哦
(SINGING) Whoa
我踏着阳光前行
I'm walking on sunshine
哦
Whoa
我踏着阳光前行
I'm walking on sunshine
哦
Whoa
感觉如此美妙
And don't it feel good
耶！
Yeah!
卡尔 你不会相信索尼娅的前舍友跟我说了什么的
DELLA: Cal, you're not gonna believe what Sonia's old roommate just told me.
你说对了 我一个字也不相信
You're right. I don't believe a word of it.
你没有确证的事实，没有目击证人
You got no corroboration, no independent witness,
而且很显然她缺钱，她的动机很明显
and she obviously has a financial motivation.
索尼娅・贝克的舍友声明…
We've got Sonia Baker's roommate claiming
她和史蒂芬・柯林斯玩三角关系
she had a threesome with Stephen Collins,
你要忽视这一点吗？
and you want to ignore that?
我不是要忽视，我只说要考虑
I am not saying ignore it. I am saying consider it.
考虑这会对我们所掌握的其他信息 产生什么样的影响
Consider how it impacts everything else we have,
考虑她有可能满嘴胡话
and consider that she is full of shit!
没错，但是， 卡尔 她还说
Yeah, but, Cal, she's also saying
史蒂芬帮索尼娅还了四万美元的卡账
that Stephen paid off Sonia's $40,000 credit card debt.
那足以写篇文章
That is a story.
这消息必须要上头版
Somebody's gonna put that on the front page.
好吧，这样做对吗？
Okay, is that the right thing to do?
听着，那部分是你负责的，是你的独家新闻
Look, it's your half of the story. It's your scoop.
由你自己决定，随你怎么做
Your decision. Do whatever you want.
但是我知道我和史蒂芬…
ANNE... But I do know that Stephen and I
一起经历了很多…
have been through far too much together
才走到今天，这一刻将决定成败
to make this one moment the thing that defines us forever.
政治前途…
REPORTER... The political future...
我试过给你打电话
I tried to call.
我打了12次，但是每次都挂掉了
I mean, I actually did call about 12 times, but I hung up every time.
你来我很高兴
Well, you know, I'm glad you dropped by,
因为我一直想和你谈谈
'cause I've been wanting to talk to you.
记得你从柏林洪堡带来的那个女孩吗？
Remember you brought that girl from Humboldt?
索蕾尔，还是叫什么的
Soleil, or whatever her name was.
露娜
Luna.
露娜，没错
Luna. That's right.
当时整个过程你们俩都被吓僵了
And you two were stoned the whole time.
对
Yep.
你成功把船弄翻了，弄丢所有的东西
You managed to flip the boat, and we lost everything.
剩下的路程都是靠走的…
We had to walk the rest of the way...
我们把船弄翻了？
We flipped the boat?
你弄翻了
You did.
那的确是次冒险
It was an adventure.
你一直都在冒险
That's what you kept saying.
爱尔兰酒
Irish wine.
威士忌？
Whiskey?
- 干杯 - 干杯（爱尔兰语）
Cheers. Sláinte.
- 那… - 那…
So... So...
- 我一直… - 我想问问…
I've been... I wanted to ask...
- 抱歉 - 你先说吧
Sorry. You first.
我在想…
I was wondering,
你觉得史蒂芬能瞒着你凑到4万美金吗？
do you think Stephen could have pulled together $40,000 without you knowing?
什么？
What?
这消息可能令人震惊
Well, it's a story that might break
它会直指史蒂芬正在做一些…
that basically accuses Stephen of doing something
须要直接调用大量现金的行为
that would require his having access to a large amount of cash.
我在想，他会这么做吗？
I was just wondering, could he do that?
震惊的消息？
A story that might break?
你是说和你有关的事情？
You mean something that you're involved in?
- 间接有关 - 你在做什么？
Indirectly. What are you doing?
我在努力帮助史蒂芬 努力保护你
I'm trying to help Stephen. I'm trying to protect you.
胡扯！
Bullshit!
(SIGHS)
你总是这样
You always do this.
有时候我觉得我们大家都约好了似的
Sometimes I feel like we all made this deal,
然后发现事情对你和史蒂芬都有好处 但对我不是
and it works out great for you and Stephen, and not for me.
然后等我们其他人发现之后…
And instead of us just figuring it out,
你们俩就像什么也没发生一样信步离开
you guys are just fine walking around as if nothing ever happened.
好吧
Okay.
好吧，我们再来一次
Okay, let's start over.
我来这是为了和你谈谈…
I come here to tell you that I'm thinking
我想结束这段婚姻的事情
about walking away from my marriage,
而你说的什么？
and you say what?
我说太晚了 时过境迁了
I say it's too late. We're way past this.
你作出了你的选择
You made your choice.
那是因为你不肯行动
Because you wouldn't step up.
你到底在想什么？
(STAMMERING) What do you mean?
那时不肯，现在不肯，大学时不肯
Not then, not now, not in college.
我是说，你现在在要求我…
I'm saying that you're asking me
给你一些不现实的东西
for something that's not real.
这就是我的意思
That's what I'm saying.
安妮…
(SIGHS) Annie...
我们正在按揭两处房产
We have two mortgages.
在维吉尼亚有
We have the place in Virginia.
这边的公寓也是
We've got the apartment here.
可以说，我们用上了我们的一切
Basically, we spend everything we make,
所以，史蒂芬不可能在我不知情的情况下…
so there's no way Stephen could have given anyone $40,000
给任何人4万美金
without me knowing about it.
- 安妮… - 没关系
Annie... It's okay.
我现在是个线人
Now I'm just a source,
所以别有压力
so the pressure's off.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PHONE RINGING)
- 喂？ - 那漂亮的金发女人是谁，卡尔？
Hello? MAN ON PHONE... Who's the great-Iooking blonde, Cal?
你是谁？
Who's this?
在街对面
Across the street.
我喜欢你的造型
I like your style, man.
我有消息给你
I got something for you.
你就不能走前门？
And you couldn't just ring the doorbell?
谨慎些好
Precautions.
照片里那人，我到处问过了 绝对是个小人物
The guy in the photo, I asked around. He's definitely a grunt.
我朋友过去常在保安工作的商业演出中 见到他
Buddy of mine used to see him at security trade shows.
但从来不知道名字
Never knew his name,
但他为一位叫弗雷德・苏莫斯的老前辈工作
but he worked for an old-timer called Fred Summers.
做些类似安装警报系统的工作
Does alarm installations, shit like that.
这是弗雷德的地址
Here's Fred's address.
水晶城
Crystal City.
多谢
Thanks.
“F・苏莫斯 N-203房”
苏莫斯先生？
Mr. Summers?
(DOOR CLOSES)
嘿
Hey.
你要找谁？
Who you looking for?
弗雷德，弗雷德・苏莫斯 你认识他吗？
Fred. Fred Summers. Do you know him?
他不在
Fred's not here.
- 噢，是吗？ - 是的
Oh, yeah? Uh-huh.
你住这，是他室友
You live here. You're his roommate.
抱歉，好的
Sorry. Okay.
你知道他在哪儿吗？
Do you know where he might be?
他出海了，上周他跟船出去了
He's overseas. He shipped out last week.
出海指…
Overseas like...
听着，我的确不知道他去干什么了 明白吗？
Look, I don't really know what Fred's into, okay?
他就是跟船走，然后回来
He ships out, and he comes back.
好的，你能给我带个信吗？
(STAMMERING) Okay. Could you pass a message?
以后来吧
Take it easy.
好吧，好的
All right. Okay.
嘿，乔？卡尔・麦卡弗雷
Hey, Joey? Cal McAffrey.
对，对，住嘴，听着
(WHISPERING) Yeah, yeah, shut up. Listen! Listen!
告诉比尔他必须要派些警察到566…
Tell Bill he's gotta send some cops to 566...
“车库”
“出口”
(RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(CHATTERING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(WINCES)
- 怎样？ - 完全没有他的踪影
DELLA: So? DONALD: No sign of the guy.
有他的名字吗？
Did you get a name?
公寓里面呢？找到什么了？
How about the apartment? You find something?
没有？
Nothing?
房子是一个叫弗雷德・苏莫斯的人的
Place belongs to a guy named Fred Summers,
只是弗雷德去年3月就去世了
except Fred passed away last March.
邻居说他的侄子在处理后事时…
Neighbors say that his nephew stays there from time to time
时不时在这里住
while the probate is being worked out.
只是他也没有侄子
Except he doesn't have a nephew.
你脑筋转得挺快
You're catching on fast.
卡尔，我以为我们之间说好了
Cal, I thought we had an understanding.
你应该共享你们得到的信息
You were supposed to share your information with us.
还记得吗？
Do you remember that?
唐，我去那儿是想和 一个叫弗雷德・苏莫斯的人谈谈，明白吗？
Don, I went there to talk to a guy named Fred Summers, right,
谁知道他已经死了
who I now find out is deceased.
如果我知道我要面对的是什么…
Do you think I would've gone there
你以为我还去吗？
if I knew what I was gonna be walking into?
碰巧到那里去的，是吗？
Just happened to be there, huh?
对
Yeah.
现在，你介意我回去跟进我的报道吗？
Now, do you mind if I get back on with my story?
这不是报道，这是件案子！
It's not a story. It's a case!
好，我就让你知道 一个叫曼蒂・布罗科的女孩…
And... And just so you know, a girl by the name of Mandi Brokaw,
16岁，混混，昨晚死了
16, junkie, turned up dead tonight.
可能是谋杀
Probable homicide.
她看起来眼熟吗？
She look familiar?
我在你们好心呈递的…
We got her fingerprints off of those
跟踪照片上发现了她的指纹
surveillance photos you so kindly gave us.
你好，我是朗达・希瓦 （电视文字：议员性丑闻）
Hello, I'm Rhonda Silver.
就像我说的 这就是他所谓的“进入委员会”
Like I said, that's what he called "being in committee."
我知道你昨晚被追杀
I know you got shot at last night,
而且我知道应该为你泡一杯可可汁
and I know I should be making you a nice cup of cocoa,
但我真他妈的生气
but I'm just so bloody angry!
我说，我假设，你们判断这个不是新闻
I mean, the decision, I'm assuming, was that this was not news.
我们…听着，我们不…我们担心…
We... Look, we didn't... We were worried that...
这是我决定的，卡姆，好吧？
It was my call, Cam. All right?
我当时，到现在都不信她
I didn't, and I don't believe her.
她的话毫无根据
(SCOFFS) She's not credible.
她只是在告诉我们…
She was just trying to sell us her sexy
她的朋友索尼娅・贝克的放荡生活
scrapbook photos of her friend, Sonia Baker.
她那死去的朋友
Her dead friend.
好，那么 到底为什么我们没有把这登报？
Yeah, well, why the hell couldn't we have printed that?
一个女侍应站出来爆一件性丑闻的料
A waitress comes forward with a claim about a sex scandal.
好极了，那是个A-1级的报道
Great, that's an A-1 story.
然后他否认，就有另一个报道了
Then he denies it. There's another story.
然后，然后其中一人反击 另一个报道又来了
And then... And then one of them cracks, and there's another story.
同时，大家都在关注这报道
Meantime, people are reading about it,
而且是通过我们的报纸在关注 因为我们能首先报道！
and they're reading us about it, because we had it first!
只是我们没有报道，不是吗？
Except we didn't, did we?
没有，没有 因为某个混蛋认为这不值得报道
No, no, no, 'cause some wanker decided it was beneath us.
看看她，来啊！看看她！
Look at her, come on! Look at her!
她是个小丑！这是竞选攻击！
She's a sideshow! It's a smear campaign.
这完全就是这些公司用来…
It's exactly what these companies do
摧毁阻碍他们的人的手段
to destroy people who get in their way.
真实的报道，真正的内幕 是“尖兵集团”
The true story here, the real story here, is PointCorp.
真正的内幕是这家鬼报社就要倒闭了！
The real story is the sinking of this bloody newspaper!
上帝！
Christ!
我们要应付新的管理层，卡尔
(SIGHS)
We have new management to answer to now, Cal,
而他们只关心销量，而不是是非
and they are interested in sales, not discretion.
而且我…我怎么和他们解释说 我们现在在一则新闻上落后了
And how am... How am I gonna tell them that we are now behind a story
而我们曾经有第一手资料？
we were once in front of?
好了，我们要把迄今为止得到的东西登报 就今天
Well, we're running with what we've got today.
不！不
No! No.
- 你不能这么做 - 为什么不？
You can't do that. Why not?
我们得到的资料足以上报
We've got more than enough to go with.
你发布了，就一定会打草惊蛇
You run with it, and you're gonna frighten off the wildlife.
而我们还没有把事实真相弄清
And we haven't got the rest of the story.
我屁也不关心事实真相！
I do not give a shit about the rest of the story!
我们今晚就登报
We are going to press tonight.
你还有8小时
You've got eight hours.
你看起来挺累，要咖啡吗？
WOMAN: You look tired. Want some coffee?
好，这样不错
Yeah, that's nice.
你们能等我一下吗？
Can you hold on for one second?
乔治，能和你单独谈谈吗？
George, a word with you for a minute?
- 当然，史蒂夫 - 谢谢
Sure, Steve. Thanks.
听着，我只是想你知道
Listen, I just wanted you to know
我在那天听证会上挺身发言…
my speaking up in the hearings the other day
完全没有不尊重你…
was not meant in any way as a gesture of disrespect to you
或者看轻你一直对我的支持
or a lack of gratitude for the support that you've shown me.
不，不，没关系
No, no. Not at all.
你当时的演讲让人印象深刻
It was a very impressive performance.
你有你的激情，我能理解
You have your passions, I understand that.
好的，太好了，你这么说我就放心了
All right, good. Well, that's a relief to know.
你可以尽情表现 总会有人给你擦屁股
You have your show horses, and you have your work horses.
我确信我们都可以设法坚持下去的
I'm sure we can all find a way to get along.
那不可能
There's no way.
我们不可能在期限前完成的
There is no way we can meet that deadline.
不，我们能 好了，同志们，我们现在火烧眉毛了
Yes, we can. All right, guys, we're getting our balls busted.
- 有什么收获？ - 好的，你要我们查的男人
What do you got? All right, the guy you had us check out,
多米尼克・弗伊，看起来知道大量的内幕
Dominic Foy, turns out he's a gold mine.
- 多米尼克？ - 弗伊
CAL: Dominic? Foy.
- 好的 - 我不断听到他的名字
Right. He's a guy I keep hearing about.
他就是那个在所有索尼娅哭泣的照片中 都出现的男人
A friend of Sonia's in all the surveillance photos where she's crying.
- 而且他也出现在朗达的手机快照里 - 嗯
And he's in Rhonda's cell phone shots. CAL: Mmm-hmm.
好了，这打扮是万圣节呢…
Okay, so, is this Halloween,
- 还是他是变态？ - 变态
or is he some kind of freak? PETE: Freak.
他做的是合法的公关生意
He runs a legitimate PR business.
大量的企业客户
Handful of corporate clients.
就和周末舞会那样
Just likes to party on the weekends.
特别的舞会
PETE: Special parties.
- 说说最棒的部分吧 - 好
Tell him the good part. Yeah,
大多数时间都在“每日小饭馆”里
mostly works out of the Daily Grill,
但知道它的注册地址吗？
but guess where his registered office is?
- 哪里？ - 猜猜
Where? Guess.
哪里？
Where?
水门大厦 （著名政企大楼）
HANK: The Watergate.
- 噢 - 不止呢，第413套间
Oh. PETE: Not only that, Suite 413.
和“自由倡议勋章”在同一套办公室，也是…
Same suite as the Medal of Freedom Initiative, which is...
“尖兵集团”的一家子议员游说公司
The lobbying subsidiary of PointCorp.
去对他录音采访吧
Let's get him on tape.
你要我通知罗尼带装备来吗？
PETE: You want me to call Rodney and get the gear?
对，老地方
Yeah, same place.
什么…对不起
What... I'm sorry.
你要给他录音？
You want to put him on tape?
对
Yeah.
我们是谁？警察吗？
What are we, cops now?
这就是在犯法啊
That's totally illegal.
如果多米尼克・弗伊能把索尼娅・贝克 和“尖兵集团”关联起来
If Dominic Foy can connect Sonia Baker to PointCorp,
那他一定有很大的压力…
he's gonna be under a lot of pressure
以致于他会告诉我们实情，不是吗？
to recant anything he might tell us, all right?
所以我们要给他录音，这样才保险
So we put him on tape. That's our insurance.
你怎么知道他会告诉你？
And why do you think he's even gonna talk to you?
因为他害怕
Because he's scared.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
因为我要让他害怕
Because I'm gonna scare him.
嘿，外面的是你的卡迪拉克吗？
Hey, is that your Cadillac out there?
对
Yeah.
V-8发动机，320马力 自适应巡航控制，平视显示器设计
V-8 XLR, 320 horsepower, adaptive cruise control, heads-up display?
- 没错 - 那真是辆好车
That's the one. That's a hell of an impressive car.
对，没错
Yes, I know.
你的游乐场里是什么宝贝？
What do you got in your gay-rage?
- 什么？ - 你的游乐场，车库
Excuse me? Your gay-rage. Your garage.
- 对 - 你也有同样的车吗？
Right. You drive the same thing?
- 不，没有，我有辆90年产的萨博 - 噢
No, I don't. I have a 1990 Saab. Oh.
对，我有丝绒座套 不过乘客席那边的烂了
Yeah. I got velour seats. The passenger side one's ripped,
但他还是能兜着我到处走
but it gets me from A to B, you know.
我很遗憾
Sorry to hear that.
如果我能在公共关系公司工作就好了 不是吗？
If only I could get a job in PR, right?
你到底是谁？
Who the hell are you?
你有读报纸吗，多米尼克？
Do you read the newspapers, Dominic?
- 有时候 - 好
Sometimes. Okay.
我有些东西要提醒你，明白吗？
I got something I want to run by you, all right?
这事没完，我还在调查这事
It ain't finished. I'm still working it up.
看看你对这些有何感想：
Let's see how you feel about this.
“多米尼克・弗伊，一位与国防承包商…
"Dominic Foy, a D.C. Public relations figure
“‘尖兵集团’有公开紧密关联的公关名人
"with known ties to defense contractor PointCorp
“于昨天被发现和国会员工…
"was yesterday linked to the death
“索尼娅・贝克的死有关”
"of Capitol Hill staffer Sonia Baker."
少来，你是记者？
Come on. Are you a reporter?
这样不好，这样很不好
This is not cool. This is definitely not cool.
非常不专业，我现在正坐着…
Very unprofessional. I'm just sitting here...
卡尔・麦卡弗雷，环球报的
Cal McAffrey from the Globe.
恭喜刚入职，送给你
Congratulations. Keep it.
这消息明天就上报，除非…
That's gonna run tomorrow unless
你今天就能告诉我我须要知道的东西
you can tell me what I need to know today.
- 我不这么认为 - 在后巷我有辆车
I don't think so. I got a car out the back.
我知道一个舒服、安全地方 我们可以去那谈
I got a nice, safe place where you and I can talk.
嘿，嘿，开萨博的 我什么事情都不知道，明白吗？
Hey, hey, Saab. I don't know anything about anything, all right?
我是公共人物，明白？
I'm a PR guy. Got it?
就作你的公共人物吧，两条路给你选
Be that as it may, there's two ways
这篇文章可以这样发表，多米尼克
this article can run, Dominic.
没你的名字，或者有你的名字
Without your name or with your name,
或者还有一张你网站上的照片
and maybe even a photo from your website.
那么，谁知道谁会被惹火呢？ 而且有多生气呢？
Now, who knows who that's gonna piss off and how badly?
我在努力帮你，多米尼克，明白吗？
I'm trying to be your friend, Dominic, all right?
我不想看到你像索尼娅・贝克一样 被一辆列车了结
I'd hate to see you end up under a train like Sonia Baker.
但你保证过我的名字从不见报，好吗？
And you promised never to use my name, right?
对，我说过
Yes, I did.
那地方会很舒适？很典雅？
This place is nice? It's classy?
- 我在那里会很舒服？ - 对
I'm gonna be comfortable? Uh-huh.
这是什么鬼地方？ （“美国佬旅馆”）
DOMINIC... What kind of dump is this?
你把我带到什么地方来了？
Where have you brought me?
小酒柜里没有酒
No booze in the mini-bar.
电视不能点播
There's no On Demand on the TV.
这是什么鬼旅馆？
What kind of hotel is this?
我说，有点汽车旅馆的样子，不是吗？
Little bit more of a motel, I'd say, isn't it?
没有人会在这里找到你，多米尼克
CAL... Nobody's gonna find you here, Dominic.
你酒调得怎么样，小甜豆
DOMINIC... How are your beer-getting skills, sweet pea?
给弗伊叔叔来一杯冰冻鸡尾酒如何？
You want to go get Uncle Foy a nice frosty?
- 我来给你计时 - 老天
I'll time you. Christ.
那么，我们从头开始吧
So, let's start from the beginning.
你在哪里遇见索尼娅・贝克的？
Where did you meet Sonia Baker?
为什么我们不从我的好处谈起呢？
Why don't we start with a little compensation?
那家伙刚才被吓青了脸，现在却要喝啤酒
This guy's stoned off his face, and now he wants a beer.
- 我能来杯吗？ - 好
Can I have one? Yeah.
他到底在吃什么？
What's he taking exactly?
老兄，镇静剂，这家伙胆都吓破了
Dude, downers. This guy's losing his shit.
- 为什么？ - 为什么？我帮你忙
For what? For what? Me helping you out.
我就要失去我的生意，我…
Me losing my business. Me...
这床真恶心
This bed's disgusting.
给我好处，明白？
Compensate me, okay?
好，你帮助我们侦破索尼娅的谋杀案 还要讲报酬
Okay, so you want to be paid to help solve Sonia's murder?
省省吧，好吗？我做公关的
(SIGHS) Save it, all right? I'm in PR.
我对问问题的措辞还是有所了解的
I know a little bit about phrasing questions.
为什么你不试一下这么说：
Why don't you try phrasing it like this?
我愿意在帮你们出书之后接受报酬吗？
Would I like to be paid for helping you get a book deal?
这里没人要出书
Nobody's here for a book deal.
真的？每个人都想出书呢
Really? Everybody wants a book deal.
而我想要我那份好处，明白吗？ 这样才公平
And I'd like my cut, okay? That's just fair.
你什么时候遇见索尼娅的？
When did you meet Sonia?
好处，好处
Compensation, compensation.
你是来这里说明事实的，多米尼克
You came here to talk, Dominic.
知道吗，鼠辈 我是老手而我不喜欢这些废话
You know, mouse, I'm the talent and I don't like the vibe.
所以你们不如改变一下方式，好吗？
So why don't you change that up, okay?
这房间不准吸烟
It's a non-smoking room.
是以你的名义登记的
It's under your name.
- 该给他用刑了 - 我喜欢这家伙
He's a douche. I love this guy.
我要给我律师打电话
I want to call my lawyer.
我觉得你应该觉悟了
I think you should think that through.
在这狗窝我们能收到信号吗？
Can we get a signal in this rat hole?
为什么你不觉悟？嗯？
Why don't you think it through? Hmm?
多米尼克，让我再一次把这事情说清楚
Dominic, let me just lay this out for you one more time,
因为我觉得你还没有明白
because I don't think you're getting it!
- 所以我会向你说明，好吗？ - 放松
So I'll lay it out for you! Okay? Relax.
我会向你友好并明了地说明！
I'll lay it out for you nice and clear!
报社可以把这事以任何他们喜欢的方式扭曲
The newspaper can slant this any which way they want to,
他们可以把你写成一个而且是唯一的 重要消息来源
and they can make you the one and only principal source.
你以为你那“尖兵集团”的朋友们…
How do you think that's gonna go down
- 最后会怎样？ - 肯定不好
with your friends at PointCorp? Not great.
而其他和你有关联的人呢？
And anybody else you're connected to?
别这样，请不要这样
Don't do that. Please don't do that.
你说的越多，你给我们的材料越多
The more you talk, the more you give us,
你就被保护的越好
the more protected you are.
这才是我们应该做的
That's the way we work.
而你的好处就是不被公开
And your compensation is your anonymity,
而这就是你能从我们这里得到的唯一好处
and that is all you're gonna get from us.
- 明白？ - 是的
Okay? Yeah.
好极了
Great.
好了，这边进行的怎样
DELLA: Okay, how's it going in here?
听起来好的要命 我们就要准备好了
Sounds frigging great. We're just about ready.
- 我们开始吧 - 好极了，很好
Let's do it. DELLA: Great. Good.
来吧
Come on.
我不干，我来打头阵
I'm not gonna do it. I'm gonna open the door,
然后这事让你来说
and I'm gonna let you say it.
你必须要和她谈谈
You have to talk to her.
卡尔要我们拖后期限
Cal is asking us to push the deadline.
我们实在不能再继续…
We really can't afford to keep doing
- 做这样的事了 - 他们到底在哪儿？
this type of thing. Where the hell are they?
你说得好像我应该知道？
(EXCLAIMS) You saying that as if I should know?
是啊，你不刚和他谈过吗？
Yeah, well, you just spoke to him.
是啊，他们没说在哪儿啊
Yeah, well, they didn't tell me where they were.
2万美元一小时啊
$20,000 an hour.
好…好了！
Yeah... All right!
走开
Bugger off!
该死
Shit.
就是这个男人，明白吗，从俱乐部认识的 好吧？
It was just this guy, okay, that I knew from the clubs, all right?
而他在一家公关公司工作，非常大的一家
And he worked for a PR firm, a very big one.
- 名字呢？ - 那…不，我不会把他名字说出来
Name? And... No, I'm not gonna give you his name.
他是位朋友，明白吗？他有…
He's a friend, okay? He had this, uh...
他有…
He had this...
他工作的公司有一个客户
Well, the company that he worked for had a client,
- 一个十分特殊的客户 - 名字？
a very special client. Name?
这个我可以给你，“尖兵集团”
I'll give you that one. PointCorp.
而他们需要一个特殊的人员
And they wanted a special employee.
他们需要一个女孩
They needed a girl.
我想到了索尼娅
I thought of Sonia.
你明白了吗？
You got that?
对不起 你的意思是索尼娅在为“尖兵集团”工作？
I'm sorry, are you saying that Sonia was working for PointCorp?
就像一个精心布置的陷阱
Like a steel trap, this one.
别把这消息放给其他报纸了
Don't lose her to another paper.
对，这就是我想说的
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
大声点，大声点
Turn it up, turn it up.
她是完美的人选，她很有胆识
DOMINIC... She was a perfect fit. She had balls.
- 她很聪明 - 她有欠债
She was smart. She was in debt.
而且有欠债，没错
And she was in debt, exactly. Yeah.
他们每个月给她支付2万6千元
They paid her $26,000 a month.
比他们给我的还要多得多
Whole hell of a lot more than they gave me.
- 他们只给我了20 - 这可是大新闻
They paid me a flat 20. It's big.
他们有告诉你她的任务吗？
Did they tell you what the job was?
没有，没告诉我 但是她告诉我了
No, they did not. She told me what it was, though.
她把柯林斯的事情告诉我了
She told me about Collins.
她说了她要做卧底
She told me about spying on him.
他们有要求索尼娅和柯林斯睡觉吗？
And did they want Sonia to sleep with Collins?
没有，她自己惹上这麻烦的…
No. She got on her back all by herself
然后把所有事情都搅乱了，不是吗？
and screwed everything up, didn't she?
他们怎样把她安插进柯林斯的团队的？
How did they get her onto Collins' staff?
我不会告诉你这个的，你可以死心了
That I'm not gonna tell you. You can forget it.
你可以绑架再折磨另一个人来得到这个消息
You can kidnap and torture someone else for that toughie.
- 我们有约定 - 是的
We have a deal. Yeah.
- 我的任务完成了 - 这里没有人会告发你
I've done my work. Nobody's here to screw you,
但我们必须知道国会里是谁在做这项工作
but we need to know who was working this on the Hill.
不不
Mmm-hmm.
国会的人，是吗？ 国会里，他们找到一个人来处理这事
From the Hill, huh? Well, from the Hill, they found a guy to fix it.
- 名字？ - 不
Name? No.
- 是谁？ - 别问了
Who? Leave it.
- 谁？ - 拜托
Who? Come on.
怎么，你们听不到我说话？
What, are you not hearing me?
算了吧，说出来的话…
Forget it. I'd be afraid to start that
我会连每天发动我那卡迪拉克都得小心
sweet ass Caddy every morning.
我说，如果是我在开你那辆萨博老爷车…
I mean, keep in mind if I was driving
我就会十分小心
that wheelbarrow Saab of yours,
我甚至可能把自己炸到天上去
I'd probably blow it up myself with me in it.
你见过那玩意儿吗？简直就像剪草机
You seen that thing? It's like a lawnmower.
我去给你拿瓶啤酒
I'm gonna get you another beer.
嘿
Hey.
喂
Oi.
你和那家伙睡过吗？
Are you sleeping with that guy?
我说，你在这干什么？
I mean, what are you doing here?
你和他睡过吗？啊？
Are you sleeping with him? Hmm?
还是你有男人了 你有男人了，对吧？
Or you got a guy. You got a guy, right?
当娜？
DOMINIC... Donna?
- 黛拉 - 黛拉
DELLA... Della. DOMINIC... Della.
我认识男人，也认识女人
I got a guy. Got a girl, too.
明白吗？我不想有人置身事外
Right? I don't want to leave anybody out.
嘿，史蒂芬，你怎么认识索尼娅的？
Hey, Stephen. How did you find Sonia?
什么？
STEPHEN: What?
她是怎么进入你的部门工作的？
How did she come to work in your office?
是谁…有人推荐她吗？
Was somebody... Did somebody recommend her?
你说的什么？
What are you talking about?
我觉得你被玩弄了
I think you've been played.
真的？
Really?
谁介绍你们认识的？
Who gave you her name?
- 这是怎么回事？ - 这事不是胡闹
What is this about? Don't dick around about this,
史蒂芬，好吗？ 两个问题
Stephen, all right? Two questions.
她到底怎么进入你的部门工作的？
How the hell did she come to work in your office,
还有推荐她的那个人的名字
and the name of the individual who recommended her?
菲戈斯，乔治・菲戈斯
Fergus. George Fergus.
说是他一位世交的女儿
Said she was the daughter of an old family friend.
道格・斯庞德的毕业派对
Doug Sponder's bachelor party.
还记得那家旅馆吗？“美国佬”？
You remember that hotel, the Americana?
记得
Yes.
现在就来，就自己 我在408房
Get here now, alone. I'm in Room 408.
我回头在办公室找你
I'll meet you at the office.
史蒂芬，我们已经迟到了
Stephen, we're late already.
我会联系你的
I'll call in.
史蒂芬，我们已经迟到了
Stephen, we are late already.
我会联系你的，好吗？
I'll call in. Okay.
(SIGHS)
别听你的留言信箱
Don't check your voicemail.
卡梅隆对推迟发稿的事情大发雷霆
Cameron's going on a rampage about this deadline.
我要的部分有剪出来吗？
So, did you cue it where I asked?
基本上
HANK: Close enough.
好的，伙计们 我现在需要你们离开这房间
Okay. So, guys, I'm gonna need you to clear the room.
- 也包括你 - 什么？
That means you, too. What?
我把史蒂芬・柯林斯叫来了
CAL... I got Stephen Collins coming in here.
如果你不在这里的话…
It's gonna be a lot more comfortable for him
他会觉得自在点，明白吗？
if you're not here, all right?
你不是开玩笑吧
Tell me you're kidding.
从什么时候起，这起调查的被调查人…
DELLA... Since when does the subject of an investigation
可以优先观看另一个被调查人的录像了？
get his own private preview of another subject's interview?
这简直是疯了
That's crazy!
你这是在污染这篇报道
You're polluting the story!
特殊情况
Special circumstance.
什么？什么情况？
What? What?
是因为他是议员大人？ 还是因为他是你朋友？
Is it that he's a congressman, or that he's your friend,
或者你迷恋他的妻子？
or that you have a crush on his wife?
你能让我明白吗？
Could you fill me in here?
以上所有
All of the above.
上帝，你真是个伪君子
DELLA... Oh, my God, you're such a hypocrite!
这报道我也参与其中 而你现在却要让他来…
This is my story, too, and you are about to kill it forever
永远地毁了它
by letting him come in here.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
我会把他带进来
I'm gonna bring him in.
我会让他坐下，给他看这个
I'm gonna sit him down, show him this.
我会让他留下记录
I'm gonna get him on the record,
这样我们就得到双方的材料了
then we've got both sides of the story.
(SIGHS)
嘿
Hey.
史蒂芬・柯林斯，黛拉・弗雷娅
CAL: Stephen Collins, Della Frye.
议员先生
Congressman.
认识这个人吗？
(CLEARS THROAT) You know this guy?
不
No.
你完全认不出他吗？
You don't recognize him at all?
没印象，可能认识 他在这里？
I don't know. Maybe. Is this in here?
不，另一间房 他睡着了
No, no, it's next door. He's sleeping it off.
坐吧
Sit down.
好
Okay.
“尖兵集团”想要安插一个人到你的团队
CAL: PointCorp wanted to plant someone on your staff.
这个人，多米尼克・弗伊，他找到了索尼娅
This guy, Dominic Foy, he finds Sonia.
他收了钱 余下的工作由乔治・菲戈斯完成
He takes a fee. George Fergus does the rest.
不，这不可能
No. That's not possible.
他们帮她还债 而且还每月付钱让她把…
They paid off her debt, and they paid her monthly to report back
你做的每一件都报告回去
every single thing that you were doing.
而当她没有价值之后，他们谋杀了她
And when she went dry, they killed her for it.
你怎么知道？
How do you know this?
然后我接到一通电话 我必须要去到某条街的角落
DOMINIC... And so I get a call, I gotta go down to a street corner.
我要买本杂志，我要去见一个陌生人
I gotta buy a magazine. I gotta meet some new guy.
这家伙，知道吗？
This guy, you know,
有着硬朗、粗脖子、健硕…
he's some hardcore, thick-neck, corn-fed,
海军或特种兵样子的男人，明白吗？
Navy-SEAL-Iooking guy, you know?
然后他对着我的脸大声说话，把我吓得不行
And he's all up in my face, scaring the hell out of me
因为他非常生气，而且…
because he's pissed off and...
- 什么时候的事？ - 大约一个月前
When was this? DOMINIC: This is like a month ago.
明白吗？他很生气是因为…
You know, he's pissed off because
索尼娅不再给他任何情报
Sonia's not giving him anything anymore.
那他有要求你为此做些什么吗？
And what did he want you to do about it?
他要我解决这事 他要我好像解决我的吹风筒一样解决这事
He wants me to fix it. He wants me to fix it, like one of my hair dryers.
你做了吗？
And did you?
我试过
I tried.
我试过，我给她电话，但她不接
I tried. I called. She wouldn't take my call.
我去她那里，想和她谈谈
I go over there. I try to talk to her.
她就哭了
She's crying.
她为什么哭？有人恐吓她吗？
DELLA... Why is she crying? She's scared somebody's after her?
不，她哭是因为柯林斯，她爱上他了
DOMINIC... No, she's crying because of Collins. She was in love with him,
而且她怀孕了
and she was pregnant,
她还没有告诉他
and she didn't tell him.
她没有告诉他，而且，知道吗？
She didn't tell him, and, you know,
她还害怕如果他发现了她的所作所为…
she was petrified that he's gonna find out what she did,
就会抛弃她…
and then he's not gonna want her,
抛弃她和她的孩子
and he's not gonna want the baby...
她几乎为此而崩溃，她甚至烧掉了…
She got so wrecked about it that she burned
好几千美元的支票，那是好几次的酬劳
thousands of dollars worth of paychecks.
谁会这么干？
Who does that?
我试着去让她放松
(SOBBING) And I tried to get her to just relax
让她考虑考虑公开此事
and to think about the publicity,
或者考虑全身而退 或者考虑，就是，她的任务
or think about an abortion, or think about, you know, her word.
“继续你的任务，知道你的决定…
"Just keep your word. And what about how
“会对我有什么影响吗？”
"your decisions are gonna affect me?"
然后她就死了，明白吗？ 我听说是被谋杀了
And then she's dead, you know? I hear it's a murder,
所以我不想再和这事…
and so I don't want anything more
有任何关联了，明白吗？
to do with this thing, you know?
我很害怕，我想去一个温暖的地方
I'm just terrified, and I want to go someplace warm,
我想恢复清白
and I want to come back to a clean slate.
而你们写你们的文章，最好让他们别再烦我
And you guys write your article and just get them off me.
我一文不值，我对他们一文不值
I'm nothing. I'm nothing to those guys.
你说的没错，老兄，好吗？
So you were right, man. Okay?
现在我们有证据了
And now we can prove it.
我要你作证，这样我们就能钉死这些直娘贼
I get you on the record. We can nail these mothers to the wall!
解脱了吧？我们能钉死他们，明白吗？ 我们赢了！
Sliberty? We can nail them to the wall, all right? We win!
- 对，只是… - 好吗？
Yeah. Just... All right?
(STEPHEN COUGHS)
只是…你能等我一会儿吗？
Just... Will you just give me a minute?
好的
Okay.
他需要点时间
He just needs a minute.
糟糕！
Shit!
别碰…别碰我！
Get off... Get off of me!
他这该死的…
You fucking...
救命！
Help!
史蒂芬！
Stephen!
站起来！你在干什么？
Get up! What are you doing?
- 嘿，住手！ - 不！
Hey, stop! No!
别这样，老兄！嘿！嘿！
CAL: Come on, man! Hey! Hey!
别碰我！
Get off!
你到底在对他做什么？
What the hell are you doing to him?
史蒂芬！
CAL: Stephen!
史蒂芬！史蒂芬！
Stephen! Stephen! Stephen!
- 嘿，我在努力帮助你 - 是啊，她怀孕了，卡尔
Hey, I'm trying to help you, man. Yeah. She was pregnant, Cal.
我需要知道这个吗？
Did I need to hear that?
- 是的 - 哈？你不能自己告诉我？
Yeah. Huh? You couldn't tell me yourself?
你一定要这样做？这样做很重要？
You had to do it like that? Was that important to you...
我觉得你应该亲自听到真相
I thought you'd want to hear the truth.
是啊
That's right.
你就是在寻找真相，仅此而已
You were just seeking the truth, that's all.
你就是…你就是个真相追寻者
You're just... You're a truth seeker.
仅此而已，你不能自拔
That's all. You can't help it.
这就是你，你就是个伪君子
It's who you are. You're such a hypocrite.
你感兴趣的不是帮我
You're not interested in me.
我来这全是因为你想要得到你的报道
Me coming here was all about you and getting your story.
我信任过你，你是我朋友！
I trusted you. You're my friend!
你和我妻子鬼混的时候…
You were supposed to be my friend
就应该去做一个真正的朋友
when you were screwing my wife!
你是我朋友，卡尔
You're my friend, Cal.
我决不会对你这样的事
I never would've done this to you!
我很抱歉，史蒂芬，好吗？
I'm sorry, Stephen, okay?
这些事我都很抱歉
I'm sorry about all of it.
请听我说，我一直表现得很混蛋
Please, look, I've been an asshole,
而我能理解你为此而记恨我
and I can understand why you hate me for it.
但你必须把对我的个人感觉放到一边
You've just gotta put aside how you feel about me
坚持下去，我们很接近了
and stay with this. We're so close.
这件事的每一步，我都让自己置身其中
Every single part of this, I have put myself on the line.
史蒂芬
Stephen.
史蒂芬！
Stephen!
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(GROWLS)
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
我想和菲戈斯议员谈谈
I need a minute with Congressman Fergus.
转告他我是环球报卡尔・麦卡弗雷 我交稿期限就到了
Tell him it's Cal McAffrey from the Globe, and I'm on a deadline.
(INAUDIBLE WHISPERING)
让他滚
Fuck him.
这混蛋
Asshole.
好的，我看到了 请交给他这张卡片…
It's all right. I saw that. Just give him this card
并转告他这是件直接与他有关的要事
and tell him it's an issue that directly concerns him.
先生？他要我给你这个
Sir? He asked me to give you this.
“索尼娅・贝克的家人向你问好”
失陪
Excuse me.
议员先生
Congressman.
你就是卡尔・麦卡弗雷
That Cal McAffrey.
有什么事？你怎么找到我的？
What's up? How'd you find me?
我跟着面包屑，议员先生
I followed the trail of crumbs, Congressman.
我须要你确认…
I need a confirmation from you
我们明天发布的文章里的东西
for an article that we're running tomorrow.
我被告知你建议…
I have been told that you recommended
格瑞尔・松顿去雇佣索尼娅・贝克
to Greer Thornton to hire Sonia Baker,
正确吗？
is that correct?
所以？
So?
所以，如果索尼娅・贝克实际上是在…
So if it turns out that Sonia Baker was,
收集史蒂芬・柯林斯调查委员会的…
in fact, gathering information
调查结果信息…
on Stephen Collins' committee findings
然后把它们回馈给那些…
and passing that information back
正在接受调查的公司…
to the very company that was being investigated
而那些公司共同谋划了对她的谋杀
and that company is complicit in her murder,
那么，耶稣基督 这事对你来说应该不会太好看
well, Jesus Christ, it's not gonna look too good for you,
不是吗，议员先生？
is it, Congressman?
一，不要无谓地在我面前提上帝的名字
One, never use the Lord's name in vain with me.
二，你怎么能把…
Two, how could you even assume
那个能干、天真的25岁女孩…
that a bright, naive, 25-year-old girl
当成什么，双面谍？
was what, a double agent?
麦卡弗雷先生，我极力举荐的那个女孩…
Mr. McAffrey, I went to bat for a young girl
有着我熟悉和尊敬的家人
whose family I met and respected,
那一家人看起来…
a family that seemed like
就和这个国家当初建立时一样的完美健康
the wholesome ideal upon which this country was founded.
那索尼娅・贝克的母亲姓什么？
And Sonia Baker's mother's first name is?
- 抱歉你说什么？ - 你听到了，世交先生
Pardon me? You heard me, family friend.
你真的以为你的新老板…
Do you really think that your new owners,
这些有责任心的全体国民…
these responsible corporate citizens,
会容许发布这篇…
are going to allow you to publish this
毫无根据的胡扯文章吗？
speculative drivel?
你甚至会在文末落款之前…
You are gonna be out of a job before
就丢掉这份工作的，小子
the devil can even say your name, son.
简宁
Janine.
索尼娅母亲的姓是简宁
Sonia's mother's first name is Janine.
你没有意识到重点
CAL... You're missing the point.
你没看到他的脸
You didn't see his face.
从他的脸上可以看出 菲戈斯才是这件事核心人物
I saw his face. Fergus is at the heart of this story.
这件事结束了，卡尔
CAMERON... This story is dead, Cal.
不管怎样，“尖兵集团”已经…
One way or another, PointCorp pushed
把索尼娅・贝克推到了撞死她的列车前
Sonia Baker in front of that train.
真的？问题是…
Really? The trouble is,
我们新的管理层不会让我们发布这些东西…
our new corporate owners won't let me print any of this
除非我们能让其中一个主角公开身份
unless I have one of the major players on the record.
要公开，卡尔！
On the record, Cal!
而唯一能这样做的人却不愿意
And the only person who could do that won't.
你能告诉我为什么吗？
Would you like to tell me why?
还是就因为你搞了人家老婆？
Or is it just that you shagged his wife?
或者你愿意向我解释如何、何时…
Maybe you'd like to explain to me how, when
还有为何“新传媒集团”让你变成胆小鬼的？
and why MediaCorp chopped off your balls.
这件事要多大有多大 牵涉的要多广有多广
This is as big and as connected as it gets.
不管你往那一条分支追查，都是件大新闻
You follow any fissure of this, it's a massive story.
现在你有菲戈斯，你有“尖兵集团”
You got Fergus, you got PointCorp,
现在你又有了“新媒体集团”，都有联系
and now you got MediaCorp, all connected,
总结起来 他们都在为一家国家级俱乐部博弈
all in collusion, all playing for the same country club.
我还不知道你居然也加入了这场游戏
I didn't realize you'd taken up the game.
噢，卡尔，如果在这里有什么腐败堕落 也都是因你而起的
Oh. Oh, Cal, if there's any corruption involved here, it's coming from you.
你从一开始就让自己介入到这件事情中
You have injected yourself in this story right from the beginning,
而我们都知道原因
and we all know why.
这事完了，卡尔，只要你还有关联…
It's over, Cal, as far as you're concerned.
我保护不了你了
I can't protect you anymore.
而现在，我已经不确定我要保护你了
And right now, I'm not too sure I'd want to.
你想要新闻吗？
You want the story?
是的，来吧
Yeah. Come on.
(CLEARS THROAT)
我和索尼娅・贝克的初次见面…
I was first introduced to Sonia Baker
是在2007年4月
in April of 2007.
她被聘请作为我的团队的调查助理
She was hired as a research assistant on my staff.
她是多数党督导员…
She was recommended by the Majority Whip,
来自西维吉尼亚的议员 乔治・菲戈斯举荐的
Congressman from West Virginia, George Fergus.
在那里相处了三个月之后 索尼娅和我开始了一段…
Three months into her time there, Sonia and I began
浪漫的感情
a romantic relationship.
我已经给你电邮了一份档案 那些会确切地告诉你…
STEPHEN... I have e-mailed copies of documents to you, which show beyond doubt
我党党员内部的腐败堕落
the corruption between members of my own party.
现在我知道了她被作为一个间谍 安插在我的部门
I now know that she had been placed in my office as a spy.
“尖兵集团”的触手已经伸到了…
PointCorp's tentacles reach into every corner
不断增长的民营安保产业的各个角落
of the ever-growing private security industry,
不论国内或国外
both at home and abroad.
这不单止意味着十分…
Not only does this pose a great...
而且这也违反了我们的法律
But it is a violation of our laws.
一个垄断的商业…
A monopolistic business...
…妨碍干涉，或者直接毁掉
...obstruct and otherwise destroy
我对“尖兵集团”的深入调查
my investigation into PointCorp.
索尼娅定期向“尖兵集团”报告 从而领取报酬…
Sonia was paid to make regular reports to PointCorp...
如果任其发展，我相信5年之内
Left unchecked, I believe that within five years,
“尖兵集团”会在美国国土上 拥有自己的常备军队
PointCorp will have its own standing army on US soil.
…进入他们欺诈的行径…
... into their fraudulent practices...
这样会控制我们的情报收集部门…
It will control our intelligence-gathering apparatus...
调查委员会发生了什么… 她接触到了我们做的所有事情
What happened in committee... She had access to everything we were doing
成功地让我们的调查付诸流水
and effectively crippled our investigation.
这样带来的后果十分可怕，必须要予以制止
It is a frightening vision and one which must be stopped.
不论如何，当我们之间的关系越来越亲密
However, when my relationship with her grew,
她停止了为他们收集情报…
she ceased her spying on their behalf,
而我相信他们为此杀害了她
and I believe they killed her for it.
对于这些人，这些我花费…
STEPHEN: For people like this, who I've spent
我生命的一年半时间调查的人…
the last year and a half of my life investigating...
无辜市民的生命只是用完就可以抛弃的工具
Innocent civilians are really little more than disposable lives,
就像不扔还会对他们不利一样
thought of as collateral damage.
我相信如果不是我自身职位的公众影响力…
And I believe it was simply the public nature of my position that
我的命运也会一样
saved me from a similar fate.
那么，我已经自毁前程了
So, as political suicides go,
觉得如何？
how was that?
十分感谢，议员先生
CAMERON: Thank you, Congressman.
- 你还好吗？ - 嗯
You okay? Yeah.
他被算计了
He was set up.
她为了每月2万6千美元和他睡觉，我说…
She was sleeping with him for $26,000 a month. I mean...
解脱了
Sliberty.
卡尔
Cal.
- 好了吗？ - 好的
You all set? Okay. Mmm-Hmm.
我们走吧
Let's go.
(SIGHS)
- 你还在？ - 嗯
You still here? Yeah.
我以为你已经回到位子上 在网络上发布这爆炸新闻了
I thought you would've been down at your desk blasting it online.
你知道的，这样大的新闻…
Well, you know, a piece this big,
还是通过手中的报纸…
people should probably have newsprint
呈递给人们好了
on their hands when they read it,
你不觉得吗？
don't you think?
我来作柯林斯、菲戈斯、“尖兵集团”…
I'll do Collins, Fergus, PointCorp,
大集团和政府渎职部分
and corporate and government malfeasance.
- 好的 - 你负责索尼娅・贝克…
Okay. You do Sonia Baker...
谋杀、曼蒂、朗达・希瓦…
The murder, Mandi, Rhonda Silver.
- 和多米尼克关系网，好吗？ - 好的
And the Dominic Foy connection, all right? Yeah.
- 用客观的角度 - 好的
Retire to the neutral corner. Okay.
轻轻地，谢谢
Gentle. Thank you.
先生，我是罗伯特・宾汉姆
Sir, it's Robert Bingham.
很抱歉我直接给你电话
I'm sorry to call you directly.
我要向你保证 我已经准备好去终结我们引发的一切了
I want to assure you that I'm ready to finish what we started.
再见
Goodbye.
(GARBAGE DISPOSAL GRINDING)
我最慢一小时回来
I won't be more than an hour.
- 嘿，大家伙，还好吗？ - 晚上好，先生
Hey, guys. Evening, sir. How you doing?
(TAPPING)
- 你好啊 - 今晚这玩意儿合适吗？
Hello. CAL: Is it a night for it?
是啊，我觉得是
Yeah, yeah, I think it is.
好吧，你多大了？说真的，别告诉我
So, how old are you? Actually, don't tell me.
那会让我不舒服的
It would just make me sick.
别问一个女孩的年纪
You never ask a girl her age.
听着，我看着你，我不到女孩 我只看到一个记者
Well, see, I look at you, and I don't see a girl. I just see a reporter.
- 终于啊 - 不论如何，回到报道上
(SIGHS) At last. Anyway, back to the story.
好的
Yes.
- 我在高中有一个英语老师 - 嗯
So I had this, uh, English teacher in high school. Mmm-hmm.
- 他是类似那种长头发嬉皮士的人 - 嗯
He was a kind of a longhaired hippie kind of guy. Mmm-hmm.
- 他也经常找不到笔 - 噢
He had a pen problem. Yeah. Oh.
他通过在脖子上…
He solved it by having a piece
带一个皮项圈解决了问题
of leather string around his neck,
他就把笔放在那上面
and that's where he'd keep his pen.
聪明
Smart.
所以我就想了
So I started thinking,
“我的朋友黛拉也经常找不到笔
"My friend Della's got a pen problem.
“我该怎么解决呢？”
(EXCLAIMS) "How do I solve it?"
- 然后我想到了这个 - 这是什么啊？
And I came up with this. What is it?
我叫它“努比亚公主黛拉・弗雷娅的…
I call it the "Della Frye Nubian Princess,
“我再也不会找不着笔了”的庆祝项链
"'I'm never without a pen"' celebratory necklace.
噢，真漂亮，我一直想要这样的东西
Oh, it's beautiful! I always wanted one of these.
- 干杯 - 干杯
Cheers. Cheers.
好吧，我想告诉你安妮・柯林斯的一些事情
You know, I wanted to tell you something about Anne Collins.
好的
Okay.
我刚才和她说话的时候
I was just talking to her.
安妮・柯林斯怎么知道…
How does Anne Collins know that
索尼娅・贝克一个月赚2万6千？
Sonia Baker was earning $26,000 a month?
什么？
What?
她怎么知道索尼娅・贝克的酬金是多少？
How does she know how much Sonia Baker was earning?
- 我们知道这事 - 对
We know that. Yeah.
安妮・柯林斯怎么知道的？
How does Anne Collins know that?
我是说，史蒂芬一定在弗伊的录像里听到了
Well, I mean, Stephen must have heard it in the Foy interview.
我们给他看的是经过剪辑的特别部分
We played him a specific part of that tape,
那内容没有被提及
and that figure is never mentioned.
卡尔，等等，你在干嘛？
Cal. Wait, what are you doing?
你在干什么？卡尔？
DELLA: What are you doing? Cal?
你不打算向我说明吗？
You gonna fill me in?
和卡梅隆说：“按住这篇报道”
Just tell Cameron, "Hold the story."
什么？卡尔？卡尔！
What? Cal? Cal!
该死
Shit.
罗伯特・宾汉姆是谁，史蒂芬？
Who's Robert Bingham, Stephen?
罗伯特・宾汉姆是谁？
Who is Robert Bingham?
(SIGHS)
“摄于1991年2月5日，于伊拉克 左起分别是…罗伯特・宾汉姆”
外面有警察吗？
Are the police outside?
没有
No.
1991年在科威特我救了罗伯特・宾汉姆的命
I saved Robert Bingham's life in Kuwait in '91.
那是他只是个17岁的孩子
He was a 17-year-old kid.
他是个好士兵
He was a good soldier.
他为他所做的一切感到自豪
He was proud of what we did.
军队就是他的生命 而当他退伍的时候遇到了问题
The Army was his life, and he had problems when he got discharged.
所以你让一个明明知道精神不稳定的人…
So you had a guy that you knew to be unstable
去做什么？去恐吓她？
do what, exactly? Scare her?
或许还使用了点暴力？
Maybe beat her up a little?
不，卡尔，我让他跟踪她而已
No, Cal. I had him follow her.
为什么？
Why?
因为我知道她有事情瞒着我
Because I knew she was hiding something from me.
因为如果我在她家
Because when I'd... I'd be at her house
如果刚好有传真来，她会变得紧张
and a fax would come in, she'd get nervous.
因为甚至在深夜的时候也接到电话
Because there were phone calls late at night.
我起了疑心
I was suspicious.
我让宾汉姆去观察她然后向我报告
I asked Bingham to observe her and report back to me.
就这些
That's all.
你是个骗子，史蒂芬
You're a liar, Stephen.
对于她的所为，宾汉姆比我还难过
He was more upset about what she was doing than I was.
你必须了解军队对于他有什么意义
You have to understand what the military means to Bingham.
他恨“尖兵集团” 就是因为它对军队所做的一切
He hates PointCorp for what they're trying to do to it.
在他看来，她必须被制止
In his mind, she just had to stop.
但她已经收手了，不是吗？
But she did stop, right?
她撕掉了那些支票 而且还为你把自己的性命投入危险中
She tore up her paychecks, and she put her life at risk for you.
对，但我当时不知道
Yes, but I didn't know that.
我不知道他会杀了她
I didn't know that he was gonna kill her.
我不知道是他杀了她
I didn't know he had killed her.
当我知道时，我的想法和你们的完全一样
When I found out, my thought was just the same as yours.
我以为是“尖兵集团”干的
I thought PointCorp had done it.
你什么时候知道的？
And when you did find out?
那我该怎么做？
What was I supposed to do?
- 找人商量 - 我试过
Tell someone. I tried.
- 何时？ - 在我去你家的时候
When? When I came to your house,
那时我想和你谈谈这件事
and I wanted to talk to you about it,
而你所关心的只是报道
and all you cared about was the story.
不，史蒂芬，我关心的是怎么帮你
No, Stephen, I cared about helping you.
胡扯，胡扯
Bullshit. Bullshit.
你关心的是如何消除因为你和安妮之间 的那出肥皂剧…
All you cared about was clearing your conscience over this little soap opera
- …所引起的良心不安 - 所以你利用了我
you have with Annie. So you used me.
- 不，卡尔 - 就好像你利用宾汉姆一样
No, Cal. The same way as you used Bingham.
我对她起了疑心，所以我让他参与进来
I was suspicious of her. I brought him in.
这就是全部事实！这是一个错误！
That's all it was! It was a mistake!
这是我的责任
It's my responsibility.
我就不应该这么做
I should never have done that.
但我从没要他杀了她
But I never asked him to kill her.
他欠你一条命
He owed you his life!
所以你才找到他
That's why you called him.
你找到他，然后就好像…
You called him, and you used him,
利用我一样利用他
like you've been trying to use me.
一个杀人，另一个掩盖真相
One to kill, and one to cover it up.
如果“尖兵集团”和菲戈斯没有聘请她
If PointCorp and Fergus hadn't hired her,
- 这些事情都不会发生 - 不，这不关宾汉姆…
none of this would've happened! No. This is not about Bingham
…“尖兵集团”、和菲戈斯的事，老兄！
and PointCorp and Fergus, man!
是关于你和你做出来的决定…
It's about you and the decisions that you have made
让四个人丧命的事
that have led to four people being killed.
当中一人当时正在送比萨饼，史蒂芬
One of them was delivering a pizza, Stephen.
卡尔，你打算怎么做？
Cal. What are you gonna do?
你知道我要做什么
You know what I'm gonna do.
知道吗，这很可笑，你那对自我价值的理解
You know, it's laughable, your sense of your own self-worth.
那是为什么？因为没有人再读报纸了？
Why is that? 'Cause nobody reads the papers anymore?
是吗？
Is that it?
因为就像某些报纸，引起了几天的轰动
It's just another story, a couple days of shitstorm,
然后就成了包装纸
and it's wrapping paper?
知道吗，在深入人们生活的…
You know, in the middle of all this gossip and speculation
那些闲聊和瞎猜当中
that permeates people's lives,
我依然觉得他们知道…
I still think they know the difference
真正的新闻和胡扯之间的区别
between real news and bullshit.
而他们乐于见到有人依然关注着…
And they're glad that someone cares enough
去给他们公开真相和报道事实
to get things on the record and print the truth.
卡尔，拜托，卡尔，别这么做，拜托
Cal. Please, Cal, don't do this. Please.
我以朋友的身份请求你
I'm asking you as your friend.
你在警察到来之前大概有3分钟时间
You got about three minutes before the cops get here.
我以为你没有报警
I thought you said you didn't call them.
我说谎了
I lied.
(KEYS RATTLING)
(GUN COCKING)
一个好士兵，要为他的国家和朋友战斗
A good soldier fights for his country and his friends.
(SIRENS WAILING)
但这些家伙，他们要把这事变成金钱游戏
But these guys, they want to make it all about the money.
你愿意在这样的世界生活吗？
You want to live in a world like that?
放下武器！
DONALD: Drop the weapon!
不管是不是我来写 史蒂芬的所为已经败露了
The story about Stephen comes out, whether I write it or not.
放下你的武器！
COP 1: Drop your weapon!
放下！
COP 2: Drop it!
我愿意付出一切
I'd rather be nothing.
我重复，放下你的武器
COP 1: I repeat, drop your weapon!
(GUNS FIRING)
“议员被捕”
“新证据把众议院议员史蒂芬・柯林斯…”
“…罗伯特・宾汉姆…”
(SIGHS)
“…‘尖兵集团’的发言人已经否认…”
“由黛拉・弗雷娅…”
“由黛拉・弗雷娅和卡尔・麦卡弗雷著” “华盛顿环球报特别报道”
怎么？你不打算发送？
CAMERON: Well, aren't you gonna send it?
再怎么说 让我等这头版4小时也不算长是吧？
I've only been holding the front page for four hours, after all.
你来发
You send it.
晚安，大家伙，明天见
Good night, everybody. See you tomorrow.
尹瑟
Yinzer.
“文件‘议员被捕’已被发送成功”
(LONG AS I CAN SEE THE LIGHT PLAYING)
“议员涉嫌谋杀”
（本片由保罗・阿博特制作的BBC电视连续剧 改编）
(MAN SINGING) Put a candle in the window
“‘尖兵集团’成为腐败调查目标”
“首席执行官辞职 面临受贿指控”
TLF中文字幕站 http://tlfsubs.eastgame.net
'Cause I feel I've got to move
Though I'm going, going
I'll be coming home soon
Long as I can see the light
Pack my bag and let's get movin'
'Cause I'm bound to drift a while
When I'm gone, gone
You don't have to worry long
Long as I can see the light
Guess I've got that old travlin' bone
'Cause this feelin' won't leave me alone
But I won't, won't
Be losing my way, no, no
Long as I can see the light
Yeah
Oh, yeah
Put a candle in the window
'Cause I feel I've got to move
Though I'm going, going
I'll be coming home soon
Long as I can see the light